<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://www.tenders.gov.au#rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>AusTender Current ATM List</title>
    <language>en-AU</language>
    <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/List</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Apr 2025 17:35:06 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <description>AusTender Current ATM List</description>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E24-586250: TRAINING &amp; SUPPORT: NATIONAL ABORIGINAL AND TORRES STRAIT ISLANDER FLEXIBLE AGED CARE SERVICES MOVE TO NEW AGED CARE ACT</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8238f55a-9c7f-44cf-824c-7111098fb88b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health and Aged Care requires the services of an organisation to provide services to develop and deliver targeted training and assistance to National Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander Flexible Aged Care Service (NATSIFAC) Providers to support the transition to the new Aged Care Act. The intent of this project is to support NATSIFAC Service Providers to:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Understand how the new Act and Rules will apply to the delivery of NATSIFAC services;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Implement and embed the regulatory changes (administrative, reporting and legislative) into their systems, policies and practices;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support their staff to understand the new requirements;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Support care recipients and their families, carers and representatives to understand what changes mean for them; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ensure all training and training materials developed are culturally safe.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8238f55a-9c7f-44cf-824c-7111098fb88b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 12080: Sourcing of film production technicians for educational and promotional content</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aa96c3f2-9823-445f-881b-494fcea58b04</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Digital Health Agency requires the services of film production technicians to facilitate the production of educational and promotional content.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aa96c3f2-9823-445f-881b-494fcea58b04</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E24-581412_RF: RFT for services to distribute Pharmaceutical Benefits Scheme (PBS) medicines under Community Service Obligation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c6fa6e29-5bb7-4707-9fa6-e4ec34383b69</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market seeks to procure the services of organisation/s for the distribution of Pharmaceutical Benefit Scheme (PBS) medicines to community pharmacies across Australia. Distribution must be conducted in accordance with the Community Service Obligation (CSO) Compliance Requirements and Service Standards. Services are also required to support the prevention and management of onshore medicine shortages. Successful organisation/s will be subsidised for the additional costs required to meet these conditions through a fixed annual funding pool.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c6fa6e29-5bb7-4707-9fa6-e4ec34383b69</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC20250454: Reef Joint Field Management Program Foundation Program Provider</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c1233fd5-0cf8-4573-9f56-ef4ad0468393</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reef Joint Field Management Program - Foundations Program Service Provider and Facilitator&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c1233fd5-0cf8-4573-9f56-ef4ad0468393</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IC0002: Industry Consultation: Electricity Metering Services Contract Terms</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4f5daca7-d74a-4a14-b061-c20d065f2969</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Finance (Finance) invites service providers in the energy industry to comment on proposed Electricity Metering Services Contract Terms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4f5daca7-d74a-4a14-b061-c20d065f2969</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC2086: Future State Architecture Design for eDiscovery Landscape</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4f365f17-1248-4988-ae37-b8936b24f895</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this engagement is for ASIC to obtain advice on the key considerations that ASIC should take into account when strategising the Future-State Design of its Digital Forensic and eDiscovery architecture. This advice is intended to guide ASIC on its long-term implementation of a future-proof design utilising best practices.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4f365f17-1248-4988-ae37-b8936b24f895</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ6575: PPIP-VAN-PVCPS Port Vila Central Police Station, George Pompidou, Vanuatu - Head Contractor (Design and Construct)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f3a78bfa-bb0c-461c-92d1-3a2c6e651c90</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Notice is for the purpose of informing Industry of the procurement for the services of Head Contractor (Design and Construct).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f3a78bfa-bb0c-461c-92d1-3a2c6e651c90</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_1361: Total R Value Equivalence for Residential Building Fabric</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5b465faf-fba7-40e3-a07a-b544d709ca44</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Develop Total R-Value equivalents for Part 13.2 Building Fabric provisions for Floors, Walls, and Roofs.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5b465faf-fba7-40e3-a07a-b544d709ca44</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSC002535: Heating, Ventilation and Air Conditioning (HVAC) maintenance</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/53d61457-3bb6-45f9-98c7-8763fa944a43</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ANSTO is looking to contract a suitably qualified and experienced vendor for the provision of HVAC maintenance across our Lucas Heights facility&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/53d61457-3bb6-45f9-98c7-8763fa944a43</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-2025-GCCA-IC-2: Second Industry Consultation Paper – Government Communications Campaign Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8d656359-7e51-4c5c-b0ea-6212f56deb2d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This notice invites interested parties to review an Industry Consultation Paper and complete a survey to provide feedback to the Department of Finance (Finance) for an upcoming tender process to re-establish the Government Communications Campaign Arrangement (Arrangement).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8d656359-7e51-4c5c-b0ea-6212f56deb2d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2024/3818: Adavale Basin stratigraphic drilling - Coring Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/559e8caf-9b9d-4d50-a485-2f3047eb3f26</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoscience Australia is seeking to procure comprehensive coring services in support of Geoscience Australia's drilling operations as described in the Scope of Services for the Adavale Basin Stratigraphic Drilling Project&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/559e8caf-9b9d-4d50-a485-2f3047eb3f26</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025012: Hot Water Plant Electrification – CSIRO Newcastle (Construct only)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8d3037dc-2cc0-45f9-aa91-ce0a54452eb6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSIRO requires an experienced and qualified Mechanical Services Contractor to manage, construct and deliver the electrification of the gas fired primary- and secondary heat source at CSIRO’s Newcastle premises as per the design developed by CSIRO. This design:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(a) uses the two existing lead-lag reversible chillers in heat-pump mode for low-temperature heating-hot-water production, with one new water-to-water heat-pump/s installed in an existing plant room to boost the low-temperature heating hot water (HHW) to a higher temperature to meet existing field terminal device requirements.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(b) Decouples the domestic hot water (DHW) system from the HHW system to a standalone central potable DHW system. The non-potable DHW system will be decommissioned and replaced with instantaneous hot water units at nominated locations.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8d3037dc-2cc0-45f9-aa91-ce0a54452eb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>25AMSA001: THE PROVISION OF AVIATION TRAINING</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/92307f6d-398d-44d2-84d4-c23522ed51c5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;THE PROVISION OF AVIATION TRAINING&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/92307f6d-398d-44d2-84d4-c23522ed51c5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-83958: PROC-83958 - Annual Revaluation Tenders for Valuers 2025-2028</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/32961510-f973-4d26-9622-92576c0e13d8</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PROC-83958 - Annual Revaluation Tenders for Valuers 2025-2028&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/32961510-f973-4d26-9622-92576c0e13d8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025015: Boolardy Homestead Airstrip upgrade project, Murchison WA – Head Contractor Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3ca6a01e-039d-41e3-a9b6-017f7bec84b9</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSIRO through this RFT is seeking responses from suitably qualified and experienced service providers for the provision of Head Contractor (Contractor) construction services for the delivery of the Boolardy Homestead airstrip upgrade project located at Inyarrimanha Ilgari Bundara, the CSIRO Murchison Radio-astronomy Observatory (the Observatory), Beringarra Pindar Road, Murchison WA 6603.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scope of the project includes, but is not limited to the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(a) Heritage protection as required&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(b) Clearing and grubbing activities for the project&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(c) Cut/fill enabling earthworks including erosion, sediment and stormwater control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(d) Extension of current airstrip pavement to 1500m in length and 23m in width&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(e) Re-grade and seal of airstrip with tie-in cross-strip (runway2)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(f) New sealed taxi-way and parking apron&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(g) Marking of sealed airstrip, taxi-way and parking apron&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(h) Amend and match existing fencing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(i) Floodlighting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(j) Relocation of departure lounge (a demountable) and an existing Illuminated Wind Direction Indicator&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(k) Potential (cost dependant) new fencing, vehicle and pedestrian gates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3ca6a01e-039d-41e3-a9b6-017f7bec84b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFP-48897: Pacific Maritime Security Program - Pacific Maritime Support Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0c06c63a-e041-4092-9ab4-beccb6f4cfa6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of maintenance and support services for Guardian Class boats and other vessels&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0c06c63a-e041-4092-9ab4-beccb6f4cfa6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2024_3065: Development of a collision risk assessment framework for Australian wind farms</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c986f48b-7828-4301-9087-753f6079bcfd</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Development of an Australian Wind Farm Collision Risk Assessment Framework to predict collision risk for nationally-listed threatened species by onshore and offshore wind developments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c986f48b-7828-4301-9087-753f6079bcfd</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09953: Moorebank Military Area Building Refurbishment Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/be1de734-d9be-4114-ad67-f176a4093e60</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Moorebank Military Area Building Refurbishment Works, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/be1de734-d9be-4114-ad67-f176a4093e60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08352: HMAS Waterhen South Wharf Mid Life Refit</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c4d0cd41-201b-4c9f-b48c-6d2b41ea41a7</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Waterhen South Wharf Mid Life Refit&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c4d0cd41-201b-4c9f-b48c-6d2b41ea41a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AEC SRC005121: For the provision of printing, mail house, fulfilment and electronic communication services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/00efdd61-c441-446b-a49a-4d14fe35f946</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the provision of printing, mail house, fulfilment and electronic communication services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/00efdd61-c441-446b-a49a-4d14fe35f946</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10030860: Managing Contractor WSI Noise Insulation and Property Acquisition Program.</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/04006a36-42a6-4f17-910e-69402fe98bfc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Infrastructure, Transport, Regional Development, Communications and the Arts intends to engage the services of a Managing Contractor to plan and deliver noise treatment works and related services for the Western Sydney International (Nancy-Bird Walton) Airport (WSI) Noise Insulation and Property Acquisition Program.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/04006a36-42a6-4f17-910e-69402fe98bfc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT43424: Australian Export Awards Event Production Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/15c7b77c-2495-49e1-b6e3-8b605ec4696e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Austrade is seeking an event production agency to propose, plan, manage and deliver the 2025 Australian Export Awards National Awards Ceremony.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/15c7b77c-2495-49e1-b6e3-8b605ec4696e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4774-2024-25: Perth Airport AWS Construction – Siteworks, Concrete &amp; Electrical Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/63bca72b-c1a2-45fb-afd7-1ca13519d4e4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Bureau of Meteorology requires the provision of siteworks, concrete formwork and foundations, and electrical services to facilitate the construction of three new Automatic Weather Stations ("AWS") at Perth Airport, WA. This includes the infrastructure to connect the site to the main electrical distribution network, as well as the construction and connection of electrical circuits within the AWS sites.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/63bca72b-c1a2-45fb-afd7-1ca13519d4e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT-43449: Social Media Scheduling and Publishing Management Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c6fe3255-b2fc-4068-9998-0b76cf5bda42</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Austrade is seeking a comprehensive tool or platform (cloud based) to effectively manage Austrade’s global social media function, supporting multiple social media accounts, in a single integrated platform that enables social media practitioners to schedule, publish, tag and report on social media activity across diverse topics.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c6fe3255-b2fc-4068-9998-0b76cf5bda42</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GOODNA QLD RFI: LONG TERM COMMONWEALTH LEASE GOODNA QLD AND SURROUNDING AREAS</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/82ddf03e-fab7-46ef-86d4-83f7e6a72c6f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exceptional Leasing Opportunity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COMMONWEALTH LEASE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GOODNA, QLD AND SURROUNDING AREAS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/82ddf03e-fab7-46ef-86d4-83f7e6a72c6f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>50827: Seeker Design Study and Industrialisation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/229f5c69-3bfe-445d-91c6-5130a82ac474</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Guided Weapons and Explosive Ordnance (GWEO) Seeker Technology Development Program (TDP) aims to collaborate with Lead Industry Partner(s) and a network of Australian small and medium enterprises (SMEs), working alongside DSTG. Together, they will design, develop, and produce a prototype for an operationally effective seeker for future GWEO systems, with an initial focus on developing seeker subsystem for Low-Cost Loitering Munitions (LCLM) under the LCLM Seeker TDP. The Commonwealth plans to commence a Seeker Design Study in Q3 2025 as the first phase of this program.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Seeker Design Study may award up to two contracts to develop a detailed proposal for the conceptual design and development plan for a Low Cost Loitering Munition Seeker subsystem. The design study results will be used by Defence to develop a work package for the Seeker Prototype Development under the LCLM Seeker TDP. The Commonwealth intends to invite the Seeker Design Study participants to take part in a Request for Tender. The tender responses will be assessed against an evaluation criteria, with one entity being awarded a longer-term contract focused on Seeker Prototype Development under the LCLM Seeker TDP.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/229f5c69-3bfe-445d-91c6-5130a82ac474</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRN2025-032: Connect to Purpose Induction Program</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/603b40ee-fa19-4e0b-9cbd-d2af3b2b220c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Connect to Purpose Induction Program&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/603b40ee-fa19-4e0b-9cbd-d2af3b2b220c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MOAD ATM 4977: Exhibition Joinery</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dd7d6a34-1f69-478e-93e1-a976d2163004</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of Joinery and Exhibition furniture (for Democracy Are You In Exhibition)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dd7d6a34-1f69-478e-93e1-a976d2163004</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT1001021077: Provision of 4G mobile Duress Devices</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f4196b88-9433-4a00-afdb-2950287289d3</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Deployment of 4G duress devices for staff&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f4196b88-9433-4a00-afdb-2950287289d3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESE25/7108: Developing Critical Sustainability Skills Courses in India</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8d10eca2-9186-492f-a8ac-b7439c4a063c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The project requires research, educational design and validation, and training delivery services, to produce and implement training products that build capacity and capability in India’s rooftop solar sector and support the objectives of the India-Australia Renewable Energy Partnership.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8d10eca2-9186-492f-a8ac-b7439c4a063c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P24/461: Provision of Security Risk Assessment Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d8d97596-9bfe-40e0-9655-c4e752e2d615</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Criminal Intelligence Commission (ACIC) is approaching the market to engage a security consultant to undertake an Agency Security Plan. The Agency Security Plan will consist of an:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agency Security Risk Assessment&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Agency Security Risk Action Plan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Security Policy Remediation Project&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Commonwealth Protective Policy Framework (PSPF) mandates that all Commonwealth entities develop a protective security plan to articulate how security risks will be managed and how security aligns with the Agency’s priorities and objectives. Under the PSPF, agency security plans must be reviewed at least every two years. A security plan is a 'living' document and requires review and adjustment to ensure the goals and management of security risks keeps pace with changes in the entity and with emerging threats.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d8d97596-9bfe-40e0-9655-c4e752e2d615</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRN2025-079 A: VetPaths 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eabd3552-0e8d-4ee5-96b8-afb781d7782c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;VetPaths 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eabd3552-0e8d-4ee5-96b8-afb781d7782c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>QoL NTS 24/201: Quality of Life National Technical Service</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1f6ecde9-ba9b-49fd-bd35-50aa7f301629</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cancer Australia is seeking to contract a supplier for a Quality of Life(QoL) National Technical Service to provide Multi-site Collaborative Cancer Clinical Trials Groups with expert advice and support for the inclusion of Health-related Quality of Life (HRQOL) and Patient Reported Outcomes (PRO) measures/sub-studies into investigator-initiated and industry-independent cancer clinical trial concepts and protocols for the period 1 July 2025 to 30 June 2027.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1f6ecde9-ba9b-49fd-bd35-50aa7f301629</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HE NTS 24/202: Health- and Pharmaco-economics National Technical Service</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/26840629-a2b4-425b-a9b4-a242d0dd2d17</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cancer Australia is seeking to contract a supplier for a Health- and Pharmaco-economics (HE) National Technical Service to provide Multi-site Collaborative Cancer Clinical Trials Groups with expert advice and support for the inclusion of HE measures/sub-studies into investigator-initiated and industry-independent cancer clinical trial concepts and protocols for the period 1 July 2025 to 30 June 2027.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/26840629-a2b4-425b-a9b4-a242d0dd2d17</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPC-13806: Blockchain Analysis Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/851dd3a3-dd13-4fde-b10c-413dedf5495b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A Blockchain Analysis and Investigation Tool.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/851dd3a3-dd13-4fde-b10c-413dedf5495b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JASD/IB/55571/1: Commercially Provided Aviation Training (CPAT)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2d0461cd-31df-4a53-b705-64994bc66250</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Commercially Provided Aviation Training (CPAT)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2d0461cd-31df-4a53-b705-64994bc66250</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>57647: Army's Land Combat System (LCS) Digital Design (DD) Program</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bd0a7a0e-e9c6-483c-b36f-bac249d3d6bc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Digital Modelling &amp;amp; Standards Management Methods&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bd0a7a0e-e9c6-483c-b36f-bac249d3d6bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025/587: Hydrodynamic Sediment Modelling Bass Strait</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5f9a9759-163f-4a4b-9f42-30099823f81f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoscience Australia seeks qualified and experienced subject matter experts to conduct hydrodynamic/sediment modelling for the Bass Strait region to inform assessments of seabed disturbance and sediment mobility.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5f9a9759-163f-4a4b-9f42-30099823f81f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN25-ELECTRICITY-WA: Whole of Australian Government Arrangement for Electricity Services – SWIS Large Market Western Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/967c0097-7ad3-4bc9-b7c0-99574b9cea4a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The provision of electricity services for Commonwealth entities in the South West Interconnected System large market of Western Australia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/967c0097-7ad3-4bc9-b7c0-99574b9cea4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 11737: Development of a curriculum for Digital Health Standards training and education.</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/72135996-075e-4c2f-b9ea-40f8cf529ba1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Through this RFT the Agency is seeking a&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;supplier who can &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;develop curriculum for &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;digital health &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;standards education.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/72135996-075e-4c2f-b9ea-40f8cf529ba1</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025/12427: X-Ray Diffraction (XRD) analysis of sediment samples</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3d74cac0-07ac-497f-900c-a50851607d49</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market (ATM) is for the provision of: X-Ray Diffraction (XRD) analysis of sediment samples.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3d74cac0-07ac-497f-900c-a50851607d49</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025-14443: Sample Preparation and Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cd6a386b-40a7-4177-b85d-35fe066495df</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market (ATM) is for the provision of: Sample Preparation and Analysis for the Geoscience Australia Critical Minerals Hub project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cd6a386b-40a7-4177-b85d-35fe066495df</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_1467: Development of a proposed implementation plan for Elevating Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander knowledge systems</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/865e2868-aa20-4eb5-92cb-2d3948c8ecf1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A three-part part project to inform National Science and Technology Council advice on an implementation plan for Priority 3 of the National Science and Research Priorities: Elevating Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander knowledge systems.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/865e2868-aa20-4eb5-92cb-2d3948c8ecf1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RAMEOL062023: Autonomous Guided Vehicle (AGV) Fleet and Ongoing Support</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4e37d61a-4967-43cb-8fa3-85a7a7f2f627</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision, installation, commissioning and ongoing support of a fleet of Autonomous Guided Vehicles (AGVs) to replace the Royal Australian Mint's (RAM’s) existing fleet, at RAM’s site in Deakin, ACT.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4e37d61a-4967-43cb-8fa3-85a7a7f2f627</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 2024-25 05: Expert workplace relations consultant</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/e94bf2fc-5731-49dc-ba38-33d2589e365f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Australia is the Australian Government’s principal arts investment and advisory body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking the services of an expert consultant to support the development of Creative Workplaces’ ‘Fair, Safe &amp;amp; Respectful Framework’ and related resources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/e94bf2fc-5731-49dc-ba38-33d2589e365f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-2582: National Disability Insurance Agency (NDIA) - Workforce Management (WFM) system</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/34503d3a-69ca-4ce8-95ab-fbc795a1a751</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The NDIA is seeking tenders for a solution to replace its existing workforce management system.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The NDIA is seeking a solution that is flexible and capable of meeting reporting, useability, and accessibility requirements.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/34503d3a-69ca-4ce8-95ab-fbc795a1a751</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proc-9177242: National leading practice management of stored grain pests</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/e37c8e2f-b5a3-41aa-93a1-b4a6fa30e54e</link>
      <description>&lt;p class="IMONormal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Grains Research and Development Corporation (GRDC) is seeking suitably qualified organisations to deliver a nationally coordinated program for resistance monitoring and best-practice management of stored grain pests. This investment builds on the success of previous programs and aims to safeguard the effectiveness of key fumigants, including phosphine and sulfuryl fluoride, while ensuring compliance with market access requirements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="IMONormal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The successful tenderer will be required to:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ListBullet1"&gt;&lt;!-- [if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;Conduct national resistance monitoring for key stored grain pests, using scientifically validated sampling and testing methodologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ListBullet1"&gt;&lt;!-- [if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;Develop and refine fumigation protocols for high-sorptive grains such as canola, ensuring practical solutions for growers and bulk handlers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ListBullet1"&gt;&lt;!-- [if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;Enhance rapid diagnostic testing to enable early detection of strong resistance and emerging threats.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ListBullet1"&gt;&lt;!-- [if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;Provide evidence-based recommendations on treatment strategies to maintain fumigant efficacy and prevent control failures.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="ListBullet1"&gt;&lt;!-- [if !supportLists]--&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;middot;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;!--[endif]--&gt;Deliver a targeted communication and extension program to support industry adoption of best-practice resistance management strategies (working with the National Grain Storage Development and Extension (NGSDE) Team, PRB2412-001SAX).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p class="IMONormal"&gt;&lt;span&gt;The outcomes of this investment will help reduce post-harvest losses, maintain grain quality, and support the long-term profitability of Australia&amp;rsquo;s grain industry. GRDC encourages applications from research institutions and industry organisations with demonstrated expertise in resistance monitoring, grain storage pest management, and extension activities.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/e37c8e2f-b5a3-41aa-93a1-b4a6fa30e54e</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10514: Lismore Remediation &amp; Refurbishment Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/06168fd5-166d-46f3-b8df-7411e12c2728</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lismore Remediation &amp;amp; Refurbishment Works, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/06168fd5-166d-46f3-b8df-7411e12c2728</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ6580: ESTL0400PH3 - AFVFP Stage 3 - Request for Tender - Design Services Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f473674b-d7f2-4679-ae23-7635021ff885</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Project No: ESTL0400PH3&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;ESTL0400PH3 – Armoured Fighting Vehicles Facilities Program – Stage 3&amp;nbsp; – Request for Tender – Design Services Contract&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f473674b-d7f2-4679-ae23-7635021ff885</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 10030764: Projectionist Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/210d27a8-7d3b-4696-a8c7-6b089857d5fe</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market (ATM) is for the provision of projectionist services to deliver technical services including film/video/digital projection in the Classification Board.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/210d27a8-7d3b-4696-a8c7-6b089857d5fe</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177216: NGN Summer Planter Workshops</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/36074dd8-3fdc-440a-b1bc-eb32b6736387</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Procurement concept came from an NGN Forum in South East Queensland. The participants identified that optimal emergence and establishment of summer crops can be impacted by the seeder setup and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A series of workshops has been conducted for optimal set up and maintenance of seeders for winter crops, and these received positive feedback. The workshops will focus on optimising planter setup to improve establishment of Sorghum, Mungbeans and any other locally relevant summer crops.&amp;nbsp; This will be supported by extension of existing research that is related to improving success of locally relevant summer crops.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/36074dd8-3fdc-440a-b1bc-eb32b6736387</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NYP2026-A: National Youth Parliament 2026</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6121ede6-5d66-48b6-949c-401ccbde643d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Department of the House of Representatives is seeking a suitable qualified and experienced service provider to develop and deliver a National Youth Parliament to be held in Canberra in 2026. The provider will deliver a five-day educational program for 150 senior students, one per each federal electorate, inclusive of adherence to child safety requirements and best practice educational outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6121ede6-5d66-48b6-949c-401ccbde643d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KATOOMBA NSW EOI: LONG TERM COMMONWEALTH LEASE KATOOMBA AND SURROUNDS, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b3809fa6-7df7-4db6-9b38-11c9c6966d3a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exceptional Leasing Opportunity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COMMONWEALTH LEASE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;KATOOMBA AND SURROUNDS, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b3809fa6-7df7-4db6-9b38-11c9c6966d3a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM 2025 1501: Research Paper (Contemporary definition of community)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2afef65f-1bc6-472e-8e98-9ae15deebc22</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Research Paper (Contemporary definition of community)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2afef65f-1bc6-472e-8e98-9ae15deebc22</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AITKENVALE QLD EOI: LONG TERM COMMONWEALTH LEASE AITKENVALE, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2cc17606-2d0c-4177-aee9-98e446c47074</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exceptional Leasing Opportunity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;COMMONWEALTH LEASE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;AITKENVALE AND SURROUNDS, QLD&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2cc17606-2d0c-4177-aee9-98e446c47074</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRQ0005104: Provision of APRA AC Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/957e541e-5cb0-4065-ab80-45b035a853f1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This tender is for the service and maintenance contract of Air Conditioning (AC) PAC Units for APRA at its Sydney office located at 1 Martin Street.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/957e541e-5cb0-4065-ab80-45b035a853f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUKUS02-2025-ITR: AUKUS Maritime Innovation Challenge 2025: Undersea Communications and Autonomy</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/98d4b97b-5b2b-4120-b09f-785ee9d1ee84</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Invitation to Register for AUKUS Maritime Innovation Challenge 2025: Undersea Communications and Autonomy&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/98d4b97b-5b2b-4120-b09f-785ee9d1ee84</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_3882: Decision support tool for assessing collision mortality impacts</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4e216724-38b2-45e4-80a0-8a59ba18f6b6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Development of a decision support tool to assess the impact of predicted fatalities caused by collision with onshore wind turbines on nationally threatened bird and bat populations.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4e216724-38b2-45e4-80a0-8a59ba18f6b6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2024_3473 2: Post construction data collection and analysis to support the onshore wind farm industry</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d0bb6164-43ce-4415-b867-7af251d0a957</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project seeks to collect and analyse post construction fatality data from onshore wind farms across Australia to &amp;nbsp;assess the collision mortality impact on bird and bat species and evaluate the adequacy of monitoring methodologies and data collection being used to achieve this.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d0bb6164-43ce-4415-b867-7af251d0a957</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNP-BNP-2425-011: Plumbing and Septic Pump Out Services, Repairs and Maintenance for Booderee National Park</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/77c705f0-18c4-4199-9779-b21708ac893e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Plumbing and Septic Pump Out Services, Repairs and Maintenance for Booderee National Park.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/77c705f0-18c4-4199-9779-b21708ac893e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT-43377: Events Management Digital Solution</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6b081f0b-b9b1-4b6f-a00b-2dbdbc4442bc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Austrade is seeking to implement the continuation of a SaaS solution to provide robust event management capabilities for virtual, physical and hybrid events. What we are looking for is a solution that will allow Austrade to deliver:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a digital-first attendee journey for physical events; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;allow attendees to walk away with insights and knowledge about markets and with new international connections for business, not a negative experience where technical difficulties limit engagement before, during and after the virtual/hybrid event.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6b081f0b-b9b1-4b6f-a00b-2dbdbc4442bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NMAT 2425-21: Incoming Freight and Logistics services for Hallyu - The Korean Wave exhibition</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bfbd1921-c64d-4f50-bd49-683d96e37737</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Procurement of Freight and Logistics Services for Hallyu - The Korean Wave exhibition to be displayed at the National Museum of Australia from December 2025 to May 2026&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bfbd1921-c64d-4f50-bd49-683d96e37737</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09928: Defence Science &amp; Technology Edinburgh Building Replacement, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/043bcd08-8767-4a54-aa7b-6a18cb18fd6a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence Science &amp;amp; Technology Edinburgh Building Replacement works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/043bcd08-8767-4a54-aa7b-6a18cb18fd6a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 2024-25 07: Children's engagement with arts and creativity</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/a10c8c8e-df33-44df-b834-d147fd529e41</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Australia is the Australian Government’s principal arts investment and advisory body. We are currently seeking proposals for a research services provider to conduct a study examining children’s engagement with arts and creativity.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/a10c8c8e-df33-44df-b834-d147fd529e41</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025019: Enabling Resilience Investment Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d1240ac9-906c-4330-bba4-ea5c45e26511</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Enabling Resilience and Investment Panel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d1240ac9-906c-4330-bba4-ea5c45e26511</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>58249: Domestic manufacturing of HF-1 steel bars in compliance with MIL-S-70703 and MIL-S-50783</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/84a1c8fe-0f20-41ca-9d99-c4eb5fcd9b3c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Request for Quotation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/84a1c8fe-0f20-41ca-9d99-c4eb5fcd9b3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFAT-1049: Kiribati Climate Resilient Rural Development (CRRD)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/591c73a6-8711-46c6-a1a4-58c997b0a629</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The goal of Kiribati Climate Resilient Rural Development (CRRD) program is to support inclusive climate and disaster resilient development on Kiribati’s outer islands through enhanced food, water and energy security. The program will deliver small-scale climate and disaster resilience projects in select communities across outer islands.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program will be delivered through a design-implementation arrangement requiring the successful bidder to undertake a full program design prior to entering the implementation phase.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The program will be valued up to $20 million over an initial 4-year period (2025-29), with options for up to $50 million and up to a total 10-year period.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/591c73a6-8711-46c6-a1a4-58c997b0a629</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-2024-25-00231: Luxury Coach with Driver Services with COMCAR</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d12d0009-dc6b-416d-9c0c-8fa50cc9c294</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Finance, as represented by COMCAR Branch, is seeking to procure national Luxury Coach with Drivers services to support COMCAR’s operations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d12d0009-dc6b-416d-9c0c-8fa50cc9c294</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2183/RFT: Provision of an internet gateway security system</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6bc6b532-29b7-4776-a6bb-06e8c50c0537</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department is seeking to modernise and futureproof its perimeter security services with the adoption of Secure Service Edge (SSE).&amp;nbsp; As part of this we are looking for a contemporary and effective secure web gateway service (also referred to as proxy). The Department is seeking a new secure web gateway solution that will need to be resilient, robust, and focused on ensuring minimal impact on the Department’s 24 hour, 365 day business needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6bc6b532-29b7-4776-a6bb-06e8c50c0537</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10030934: Digital Games Tax Offset Assessment Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8f96b625-a012-49a3-a82b-b0a9dc5f2c96</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department is seeking to procure specialist financial assessment services for applications to the Digital Games Tax Offset (DGTO) over three years (2025-56, 2026-27 and 2027-28)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8f96b625-a012-49a3-a82b-b0a9dc5f2c96</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_3804: Onshore wind farm mitigation and curtailment trials</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/417473f0-8b06-484e-b7aa-c0419fabc5f6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project seeks to conduct field trials to test and evaluate various mitigation approaches for reducing the collision impact of onshore wind farms on EPBC listed bird and bat species.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The outcomes of these trials will provide assessment officers and proponents with robust evidence and practical guidance to inform the evaluation and conditioning around the design of operational mitigation at onshore wind farms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/417473f0-8b06-484e-b7aa-c0419fabc5f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_3739: Understanding Australian bird and bat overland flight paths</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9181828e-adbd-40ff-b934-ab0055a66d56</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Undertake a research report, and build a national bird and bat flight path database with spatial interactive tool to improve our understanding of the overland flyways and flight paths of birds and bats across Australia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9181828e-adbd-40ff-b934-ab0055a66d56</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-4337: Auslan Interpreting Services for Agency Staff</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ced5e408-a431-4678-b8c8-b9b4559c9211</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Disability Insurance Agency (the Agency) is seeking submissions for the provision of Auslan interpreting services for staff.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ced5e408-a431-4678-b8c8-b9b4559c9211</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DHA-PROC-85016: SUPPLIER EOI FOR NEW BUILDS VOLUME LEASING PROGRAM IN BRISBANE, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f6911a2-1fca-47ca-8bd9-2718aff61cd9</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence Housing Australia (DHA) is seeking Expressions of Interest (EOI) from interested parties active in the development of land, building and/or sale of new dwellings to investors, or investment bodies looking for secure long-term leases on properties in their investment portfolios to deliver a proposed New Builds Volume Lease Program in Brisbane, Queensland (QLD).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f6911a2-1fca-47ca-8bd9-2718aff61cd9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proc-9177246: Coordinator - Soilborne Disease Initiative (SBDI)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/aef66e67-be73-4cf0-8599-91594cf0fdfe</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Soilborne Disease Initiative (SBDI) is a strategic investment aimed at addressing the significant yield losses caused by soilborne pathogens in Australian grains. These diseases impose an annual yield loss of over $1.71 billion across all grains, with $1.23 billion in wheat alone. Current management strategies are limited by genetic resistance, chemical control options, and crop rotation constraints.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To ensure a collaborative national effort, the SBDI will be facilitated by a National Co-ordinator. This co-ordinator will facilitate and organise the annual SBDI research forum, provide support and quality assurance for all reporting and communication from programs for the GRDC Initiative Manager, and chair the annual Program Advisory Committee (PAC).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/aef66e67-be73-4cf0-8599-91594cf0fdfe</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10519: Singleton Mess Refurbishment, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f1c332dc-78d4-4e6e-ac6a-1b99fa89a8af</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Singleton Mess Refurbishment, NSW&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f1c332dc-78d4-4e6e-ac6a-1b99fa89a8af</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_3801: Onshore species-specific research and guidance to support onshore renewable energy industries</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a513d4d6-c3a9-4d66-83e1-216bd08e5dac</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project seeks to collect and collate critical ecological information required for EPBC Act assessment and develop associated regulatory guidance for 36 priority threatened species (see associated ATM documents for further information). This work will support the speed and rigour with which renewable energy projects can assessed under the EPBC Act.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a513d4d6-c3a9-4d66-83e1-216bd08e5dac</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTICE DHA-85016: NOTICE OF INTENDED PROCUREMENT - SUPPLIER EOI FOR NEW BUILDS VOLUME LEASING PROGRAM IN BRISBANE, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4849681f-1ff0-4a70-86ab-468fb5a5dbbf</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence Housing Australia (DHA) is issuing this Notice of Intended Procurement (NOIP) for our upcoming Brisbane - QLD New Builds Volume Leasing Program Expression of Interest (EOI).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4849681f-1ff0-4a70-86ab-468fb5a5dbbf</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHFT24018: Managing Contractor - Marine Assets Maintenance and Renewal Works Project</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4e035795-3e5b-4817-8a34-6c454e93aabb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Managing Contractor - Maintenance and RenewalWorks – Marine Structures - Cockatoo Island, Woolwich Dock, Sub Base Platypus.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4e035795-3e5b-4817-8a34-6c454e93aabb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSD/RFT/55619/1: ATM for Designer Support Contract Services - Maritime West</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3ad4f369-4eef-48af-9413-dbe66113442f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The procurement of specialised through-life engineering designer support&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3ad4f369-4eef-48af-9413-dbe66113442f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177244: NGN Water quality impacts on herbicide efficacy.</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/26698d4c-f142-4f5e-bc3e-6098d5e6fd78</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The quality of water used in spraying operations is essential for achieving optimal weed control in cropping systems. Reduced herbicide efficacy can significantly contribute to herbicide resistance in weeds and negatively affect profitability if spray applications do not effectively reduce&amp;nbsp; the weed population.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Enhancing growers' understanding of water quality test results will enable them to make more informed weed management decisions, which could involve either improving water quality or making appropriate herbicide choices.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This issue has been raised by growers at Northern Region NGN forums in 2023 and 2024 and is a matter of concern.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/26698d4c-f142-4f5e-bc3e-6098d5e6fd78</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST07527: RAAF Richmond Infrastructure Relocation, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6abcdcfc-450f-44aa-aa25-91e8fd1c9b60</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RAAF Richmond Infrastructure Relocation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6abcdcfc-450f-44aa-aa25-91e8fd1c9b60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025002: Cleaning Services Tasmania</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0ce38cf7-8ac4-4eca-8be7-683094677440</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSIRO through this RFT is seeking responses from suitably qualified and experienced service providers for the provision of cleaning services (Services) in Hobart, Tasmania, for a contract term of 3-years with two possible extension options of 2-years each.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0ce38cf7-8ac4-4eca-8be7-683094677440</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JASD/EOI/55571/1: Commercially Provided Aviation Training (CPAT)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9671c75b-254e-4354-88d3-ffd465de956f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Commercially Provided Aviation Training (CPAT)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9671c75b-254e-4354-88d3-ffd465de956f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>P24/429: Request for Information – Intelligence Analysis Capability</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bc22e3c8-4b96-46b7-8619-de5bff1988e1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Criminal Intelligence Commission (ACIC) provides unique and incisive intelligence to combat the threats Australia faces from transnational serious and organised crime. Our integrated view of crime is made possible through connected systems and capabilities that are used to coordinate decision making with state and territory, Commonwealth and international partners.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bc22e3c8-4b96-46b7-8619-de5bff1988e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPG009: Provision of Security Guarding Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9d340bf2-e792-440c-9c46-8fcfb95b00db</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of a Security Guarding Service provider for their purpose-built building located adjacent to the High Court of Australia and the National Gallery of Australia in the Arts &amp;amp; Civics Campus of the Parliamentary Triangle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9d340bf2-e792-440c-9c46-8fcfb95b00db</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFAT-1052: Indonesia Infrastructure and Climate Finance Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fe9e045a-ab49-4077-9acf-f2d3c24ee221</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Indonesia Infrastructure and Climate Finance Investment&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fe9e045a-ab49-4077-9acf-f2d3c24ee221</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25167: Market Deep Dives</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ccfcae4-f257-40fa-aafe-9046779752fc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To assist Tourism Australia with the developement and delivery of a report that provides a deep dive into Australias key markets&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ccfcae4-f257-40fa-aafe-9046779752fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177230: Enhancing productivity and profitability in farming systems in Central NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/93cc54ec-3dcc-4498-ba21-85cfb1d44969</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The investment aims to reduce yield gaps in the Central NSW sub-regions by addressing key farming decisions related to nutrition, crop protection, and planting. Activities will be tailored to local conditions, leveraging professional agronomists, research, and extension resources to enhance productivity and profitability. Hyper-yielding aspects and resource efficiencies will also be examined to understand environmental and sustainability aspects.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This investment will adopt a participatory approach with growers and advisors to identify and address issues most relevant to the targeted regions. The process will involve identifying constraints, referencing existing research, developing new practices, and implementing action plans. Monitoring and evaluating project outcomes through on-farm trials and demonstrations will be integral to this approach. Peer-to-peer learning and the guidance of research and consulting agronomists will help growers understand and implement necessary changes.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Regional strategies and localised action plans will be continually reviewed and refined to build growers' knowledge and confidence, promoting practice change and adoption. Extension activities will support knowledge for decision-making, utilising multiple channels such as field walks, presentations, webinars, and podcasts. A detailed monitoring and evaluation plan will measure progress and effectiveness, ensuring that activities are impactful for growers and align with the five-year goal of reducing yield gaps.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/93cc54ec-3dcc-4498-ba21-85cfb1d44969</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08246: HMAS Creswell HC Building Refurbishment, ACT</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/29ea4b89-5651-4c13-b8af-506a4c6c5ea2</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Creswell HC Building Refurbishment, ACT&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/29ea4b89-5651-4c13-b8af-506a4c6c5ea2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10030880: Expert Advisers – Noise Insulation and Property Acquisition Program</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b9cc317-204c-413f-b8b3-2b5c4a916d6c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Expert advisers to provide technical support services to the department in the following disciplines:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;a)&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;Acoustics&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;b)&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Building control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;c)&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Cost planning&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b9cc317-204c-413f-b8b3-2b5c4a916d6c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24AMSA270: Cape Moreton Lighthouse Stonework Refurbishment</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cfee32f4-3d1f-4e0f-8fca-8dd99cea97dd</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cape Moreton Lighthouse Stonework Refurbishment&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cfee32f4-3d1f-4e0f-8fca-8dd99cea97dd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 2024-25 06: Supporting the development of creative health practice in Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/8ffc5718-e9e5-4110-927e-4a8e12913c26</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Australia is the Australian Government’s principal arts investment and advisory body.&amp;nbsp;We are currently seeking the services of a contractor, or a consortium, to develop arts and health&amp;nbsp;infrastructure in Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Note, this project is focussed on community artists working in health settings rather than art&amp;nbsp;therapy. Art therapy is a specialised field of therapy that already has established professional&amp;nbsp;standards and a membership body.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/8ffc5718-e9e5-4110-927e-4a8e12913c26</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMSP-2022-0003-01-1: Pacific Maritime Security Program Acquisition of Enhanced Aerial Surveillance Services (Fixed-Wing)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fc3a3478-b243-4757-bbd9-79e0a55c6f5c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PMSP Acquisition of Enhanced Aerial Surveillance Services (Fixed-Wing)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fc3a3478-b243-4757-bbd9-79e0a55c6f5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCD LEWG 2025: Land Environment Working Group 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/be5f55af-acc3-46ee-9105-9f81de1a8d9d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LEWG 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/be5f55af-acc3-46ee-9105-9f81de1a8d9d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSD/RFT/41788/1: Mine Warfare and Clearance Diving Capability Life Cycle Management Support Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a95f0339-aa14-4dec-81bb-37d9dbaca450</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Capability LifeCycle Manager required to support DASSPO in Asset Management Services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a95f0339-aa14-4dec-81bb-37d9dbaca450</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVY/LSSVT/55811: Large Shiphandling and Small Vessel Training</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/15b3c89b-087c-44aa-a325-b0e10bb69fbc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Large Shiphandling and Small Vessel Training&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/15b3c89b-087c-44aa-a325-b0e10bb69fbc</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN/MASR2-RFT: Management Advisory Services Panel Refresh: Corporate and Commercial Management Advisory Services and Investment Banking</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fc33bb72-b2d9-4bf2-9fca-8f28d774ebb8</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Request for Tender (RFT) is for the refresh of the Corporate and Commercial Service Areas and the Investment Banking Services Service Subcategory of the Management Advisory Services (MAS) Panel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fc33bb72-b2d9-4bf2-9fca-8f28d774ebb8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-2024-PP1Refresh: People Panel - Recruitment and Search Services Panel - Refresh</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/28fb2d04-c332-4ec8-91c7-35fac32f2f23</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Request for Tender (RFT) is for the refresh of the Whole-of-Australian Government People Panel - Recruitment and Search Services Panel - Refresh&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/28fb2d04-c332-4ec8-91c7-35fac32f2f23</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177224: GRDC International Visiting Fellowships Program 2025/2026</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/1881c94b-0a57-41bd-8e89-7536819b1537</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GRDC has identified access to capacity in new/emerging research disciplines or access to capacity in scientific disciplines that have not historically been applied to Agricultural research as one mechanism through which to address perennial research problems and create greater value for grain growers. Further, it has recognised that the current and future research landscape requires fostering collaborative international engagement by providing enabling support to accelerate the delivery of research outputs in GRDC’s 2023-2028 RDE Strategic Plan through International Network-to-Network Collaborations involving multidisciplinary, complementary, and cross-cultural teams.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This investment seeks to partner emerging national and international research leaders from existing, new and/or traditionally non-grains focussed research disciplines with established Australian grains industry researchers to tackle intractable problems in GRDC’s strategic priority investment areas. The proposed investment program presents a broad open-call mechanism to drive further Australian grains industry access to new research capacity in GRDC’s strategic priority areas.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;IVFP goals include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1) Support for building research capacity towards activities that launch international research network of networks (NoN) that will catalyse collaboration that results in an accelerated advancement of solution to R&amp;amp;D challenges after the award period and&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2) Foster a diverse and internationally competent Australian-based workforce trained in conducting and leading multiteam international collaboration that can be harnessed to address industry challenges targeted at the GRDC’s 2023-28 RD&amp;amp;E Strategic Plan to deliver benefit to Australian growers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Proposal MUST be submitted by the Host Institution in Australia and not by the international visitor.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GRDC will award a maximum of 9 International Visiting Fellowships for the 2025-2026 financial year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/1881c94b-0a57-41bd-8e89-7536819b1537</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JASD/RFT/50036/1: Maritime Aviation Support Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d95d0de0-4d44-4982-92ee-ba688e4d309a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RFT for the provision of Maritime Aviation Support Services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d95d0de0-4d44-4982-92ee-ba688e4d309a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JASD/RFT/20200/1: Defence Search and Rescue Service Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3e95b1c4-e2c2-41e9-99db-550f558894ed</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence Search and Rescue Services (DSARS) RFT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3e95b1c4-e2c2-41e9-99db-550f558894ed</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Mar 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DemoATM2025: Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGF_17: Supply of Medical Grade Footwear to eligible persons</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NOTE: existing suppliers need not reapply&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Medical Grade Footwear (MGF) Programme is an important part of DVA’s health care arrangements and is part of the Rehabilitation Appliance Programme (RAP).&amp;nbsp; The MGF Programme provides a nation-wide access to a wide range of MGF and related services for entitled persons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPC-2017: Invitation to provide Day Procedure Centre Services to the Veteran Community</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Veterans’ Affairs (DVA) is seeking to contract with eligible stand-alone private day hospitals (referred to as Day Procedure Centres or DPCs) to provide DPC services for DVA Entitled Persons across Australia from 1 October 2017 onwards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHS-16: Private Hospital Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DVA is seeking the provision of Private Hospital services for Entitled Persons by publishing this &lt;em&gt;Invitation to Provide Private Hospital Services to the Veteran Community&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNS16: Department of Veterans' Affairs Community Nursing Services Invitation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Department of Veterans' Affairs invites interested suppliers of Community Nursing Services to apply to provide these services from 1 July 2016.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>