<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://www.tenders.gov.au#rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>AusTender Current ATM List</title>
    <language>en-AU</language>
    <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/List</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2025 16:35:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <description>AusTender Current ATM List</description>
    <item>
      <title>NMAT 2425-16: Water Spirits immersive experience and tour</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d182f215-49cf-4c6d-9aaa-ef222fdc176b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Museum of Australia (the Museum) requires the services of a premier digital production company to develop a captivating digital immersive experience. The production will tour at least six Southeast Asian countries over three years starting from May 2026, and will also be displayed at the Museum site in Canberra in July 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d182f215-49cf-4c6d-9aaa-ef222fdc176b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08259: Macrossan Camp Building Refurbishments, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a516f555-2582-40b0-8840-f46dabd78ced</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EST08259 Macrossan Camp Building Refurbishment&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a516f555-2582-40b0-8840-f46dabd78ced</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24AMSA255: Provision of vessel drift trajectory and prediction modelling system</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f6da905d-807f-4b20-bcfd-7fedbcd86de2</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The provision of vessel drift trajectory and prediction modelling system&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f6da905d-807f-4b20-bcfd-7fedbcd86de2</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RIC2025 001: Traffic Management Services RIC 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f5896889-e60e-4927-8512-ee771154d0f5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Invitation for Expression of Interest - Traffic Management Services RIC 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f5896889-e60e-4927-8512-ee771154d0f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ILSCE-24: INFRASTRUCTURE AND LOGISTICS SERVICES  FOR COMMEMORATIVE EVENTS IN FRANCE, TÜRKIYE AND AUSTRALIA (2027-2029)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/92cfc978-e9b1-4702-b776-1eee656d94d4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DVA is seeking Expressions of Interest from suppliers for the provision of Infrastructure and Logistics Services for Commemorative Events in France, Türkiye and Australia (ILSCE) (2027-2029).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/92cfc978-e9b1-4702-b776-1eee656d94d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25004GlobalMed: Global Media Monitoring services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a5e98b5d-c2bb-4c52-94e0-55b696652543</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Global Media Monitoring Services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a5e98b5d-c2bb-4c52-94e0-55b696652543</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08241: HMAS Creswell Office Refurbishments, ACT</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/240ff7ac-365c-4e01-980a-91de563b7647</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Creswell Office Refurbishments, ACT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/240ff7ac-365c-4e01-980a-91de563b7647</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1001012224: Identity Verification, Financial, Asset and Income Search Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7860136d-1418-40fe-a225-bb2911fcc06b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Establishment of an Identity Verification, Financial, Asset and Income Search Services Panel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7860136d-1418-40fe-a225-bb2911fcc06b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177111: Value chain innovation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/59fdd1ae-1cb6-4305-b1a7-f56eaa9d27e6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Due to relatively high costs associated with the Australian grains supply chain, and the various opportunities to add value within it, GRDC is undertaking an open RD&amp;amp;E call aimed at improving the enduring profitability of Australian grain growers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Request for Proposal (RFP) process aims to tackle critical challenges and opportunities along the value chain by leveraging external expertise, novel technologies, and insights. It invites proposals within the example topics provided and is also open to additional topics that fall within the nominated scope.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;By engaging a diverse range of stakeholders, including technology developers, academic institutions, and industry practitioners, the initiative seeks to drive breakthrough innovations that will enhance the profitability and sustainability along the grains value chain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Applicants must follow a limited set of guiding principles, communicated to them as part of the tender release, notably that each investment identifies a tangible outcome for Australian grain growers, a clear path to achieving this, and that the benefit is quantifiable.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/59fdd1ae-1cb6-4305-b1a7-f56eaa9d27e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177190: Fostering the adoption of variable rate fertiliser application for improved nutrient use efficiency</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/dfeee19d-bc28-4c44-a125-c5382ec7d2a5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Growers have expressed a desire for training in the use of variable rate technology (VRT) in their farming enterprises. Adoption of the technology could be increased by implementing a peer-to-peer learning approach that pairs groups of growers who have not utilised VRT with consulting agronomists that are proficient in the use of the technology on farm. A coordinating organisation is sought to oversee the implementation of this approach. Growers will be guided through a VRT journey to give them the necessary confidence and skills to adopt the technology broadly in their farming enterprise. Detailed economic analysis of the VRT activity will be undertaken to assess the profitability of its implementation along with implications for on-farm carbon accounting.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/dfeee19d-bc28-4c44-a125-c5382ec7d2a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PPIP-VAN-PVCPS: PPIP-VAN-PVCPS Port Vila Central Police Station, George Pompidou, Vanuatu – Head Contractor (HC)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b9b6b613-e0b2-4d77-af12-447b50613647</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Notice is for the purpose of informing Industry of the upcoming procurement for the services of Head Contractor (Design and Construct).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b9b6b613-e0b2-4d77-af12-447b50613647</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LCD-22-0002-AID25: Land-Air Autonomous Tactical Teaming in the Littoral at Scale (LAATT-LS)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9818bd32-ce40-4cc0-a932-93623a5cab14</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Land-Air Autonomous Tactical Teaming in the Littoral at Scale (LAATT-LS)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9818bd32-ce40-4cc0-a932-93623a5cab14</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09329: RAAF Edinburgh Building Refurbishments, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3e905194-67e2-4a10-9965-8908512b4d19</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RAAF Edinburgh Building Refurbishments, SA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3e905194-67e2-4a10-9965-8908512b4d19</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10510: Palmer Barracks Infrastructure Works, WA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/48309016-de17-46bd-8edd-9d296084446a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Palmer Barracks Infrastructure Works, WA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/48309016-de17-46bd-8edd-9d296084446a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NS1246 RFI: Global Protective Security Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/57e51ffe-7b06-4a64-baf7-fcca8ad02946</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ABC Security is approaching the market for a Protective&lt;br&gt;Security Services contractor(s) to provide (comprehensive/broad spectrum) specialist security (and risk management) services internationally and domestically&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/57e51ffe-7b06-4a64-baf7-fcca8ad02946</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>48897: Pacific Maritime Security Program - Pacific Maritime Support Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dfe075c4-49e0-41af-bbe2-7cbda1fcb6df</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of maintenance and support services for Guardian Class Patrol Boats and other Vessels.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dfe075c4-49e0-41af-bbe2-7cbda1fcb6df</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEG-CFI-20230901B: Construction Market Sounding Process - Defence Capital Works Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e40306e1-f5c0-4dad-a9b8-c908b175868a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To assist the Commonwealth of Australia (&lt;strong&gt;Commonwealth&lt;/strong&gt;), represented by the Department of Defence, in considering the potential delivery of Anticipated Works, the Commonwealth invites participation in a market sounding process in accordance with the attached market sounding document (&lt;strong&gt;Market Sounding&lt;/strong&gt;) from persons or entities interested in participating in the delivery of the Anticipated Works (&lt;strong&gt;Respondent&lt;/strong&gt;).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e40306e1-f5c0-4dad-a9b8-c908b175868a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEG-CFI-20230901A: Design Services Market Sounding Process - Defence Capital Works Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5c2c1e-fea6-440c-9c3a-996262c3fd60</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Commonwealth of Australia (&lt;strong&gt;Commonwealth&lt;/strong&gt;), represented by the Department of Defence, is considering the potential delivery of works in response to the Defence Strategic Review (&lt;strong&gt;Anticipated Works&lt;/strong&gt;). The Commonwealth invites participation in a market sounding process for design services for the Anticipated Works (&lt;strong&gt;Design Services&lt;/strong&gt;) in accordance with the attached document (&lt;strong&gt;Market Sounding&lt;/strong&gt;) from persons or entities interested in participating in the provision of Design Services (&lt;strong&gt;Respondent&lt;/strong&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Further information is available in the attached market sounding form accessible by clicking the 'ATM Documents' link on this page.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5c2c1e-fea6-440c-9c3a-996262c3fd60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>24/713-09-OT: CoreMod SI - Application Migration</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ab3fb758-d4d6-4bce-bffc-f2c3b992ca3c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Bank's Core Modernisation Program (CoreMod) program seek&amp;nbsp; services&amp;nbsp; to transition all in-scope applications from the Bank’s legacy data centres&amp;nbsp; to the target state environments.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ab3fb758-d4d6-4bce-bffc-f2c3b992ca3c</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health_E24-581412_No: Services to distribute Pharmaceutical Benefits Scheme medicines in accordance with the Community Service Obligation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bafce0a5-c6f4-4d2c-b9d3-904e56b90592</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Department of Health and Aged Care intends to release a RFT to the open market in February 2025. The RFT (anticipated AusTender ATM ID: Health/E24-581412_RFT) will be to procure the services of organisation/s for the distribution of PBS medicines to community pharmacies across Australia in accordance with the CSO Compliance Requirements and Service Standards. Services are also required to support the prevention and management of onshore medicine shortages. Successful organisation/s will be subsidised for the additional costs required to meet these conditions through a fixed annual funding pool. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bafce0a5-c6f4-4d2c-b9d3-904e56b90592</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSD/RFT/39046/1: Air Component Command and Control Capability System In-Service Support Contract 2025-2035</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c0c076da-0416-4b2c-9397-0802ac5dbb4c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Services in support of the Air Component Command and Control Capability System (AC-C2CS)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c0c076da-0416-4b2c-9397-0802ac5dbb4c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E22-298551: Enhance application and integrate the IAR-DST Into General Practice software</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c52d9141-f857-4b3f-ad15-2262d5c0b914</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department is seeking Proposals for the following Services:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhanced application of the Initial Assessment and Referral for Mental Health Decision Support Tool (IAR-DST);&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Enhancements that could be made to the IAR to improve its functionality within the stepped system of care;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Integration of the IAR-DST into General Practice software;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Utilisation of the IAR-DST for data collection to inform policy decisions for investment in the primary mental health care sector; and&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Translation research that could be utilised with any data collected from IAR?DST outcomes.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c52d9141-f857-4b3f-ad15-2262d5c0b914</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2024/3870: Sample Audit and Process Uplift</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed20d95a-0ed0-4130-9050-14d8e8f2be7b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Sample Audit and Process Uplift&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed20d95a-0ed0-4130-9050-14d8e8f2be7b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM 2024 0838: ASA Space Capabilities and Services Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1589b513-0374-433a-8e4e-f928a7598648</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Establishment of a Space Capabilities and Services Panel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1589b513-0374-433a-8e4e-f928a7598648</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HH-AF 2425-01: Book Publishing and Distribution Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c14c13e1-dcf2-4c8e-b032-87b8f9512beb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;History and Heritage - Air Force requires print and digital book design, production and marketing services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c14c13e1-dcf2-4c8e-b032-87b8f9512beb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NNSD/RFI/54564/1: Request for Information – Warehousing Solution – Osborne Precinct</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ec59b50-77f3-4127-82cb-5a5894536344</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this Request For Information (RFI) is to obtain information in connection with a warehousing solution to support continuous naval shipbuilding and sustainment activities at the Osborne (South Australia) precinct.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ec59b50-77f3-4127-82cb-5a5894536344</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GWEO/RFP/54912/1: Expendable Undersea Countermeasures</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eeac40c5-e755-4640-a66c-c7bec27ab00b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Expendable Undersea Countermeasures&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eeac40c5-e755-4640-a66c-c7bec27ab00b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2024_0983: Space Situational Awareness (SSA) Capabilities for Launch and Return Support in Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/308ebb91-32a5-4508-b9b0-099b77b64254</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Industry capability for monitoring launches and return support.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/308ebb91-32a5-4508-b9b0-099b77b64254</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25041: Global Stand Build Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b0b23b90-9276-4beb-ad28-0101ed2950e6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Global Stand Build Services Panel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b0b23b90-9276-4beb-ad28-0101ed2950e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177170: Reducing Post Maturity Yield Loss Risk- Program 1: Measurement and rating system for canola pod shatter resistance trait</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/d5701ce6-ffb1-4971-97e2-719b96e8b459</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GRDC is looking to invest in the development of an accurate pod shatter measurement and a rating system, which will enhance grower confidence and aid in the selection of appropriate cultivars, ultimately minimising the risk of yield loss during the post-grain filling stage in canola. Additionally, the investment will refine national estimates on the frequency and severity of pod shatter in canola. This will enhance the value proposition for Australian canola breeders targeting pod-shatter resistance and provide advice for growers concerning cultivar choice and management decisions&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/d5701ce6-ffb1-4971-97e2-719b96e8b459</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09281: RAAF Williamtown Medical Centre Refurbishment, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5a8168c5-932a-4fa3-931b-7c5781643ee5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RAAF Williamtown Medical Centre Refurbishment&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5a8168c5-932a-4fa3-931b-7c5781643ee5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177186: Reducing the frost sensitivity of Canola in Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/b7371025-74f9-4cbd-8a7b-3c52766d48f1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Canola is one of the most important oilseed crops in the world with its versatility of use for human food consumption as well as its industrial uses and is only second to soybean in volume of production (Wrucke et al. 2019a, b). There are three growth habits found in canola: spring, winter and semi-winter with the dominant types in Australia being winter and spring types with long season types better adapted to high rainfall zones whilst short season types are better adapted to areas with less rainfall and harsher temperature extremes (Lilley et al. 2019; Wrucke et al, 2019a, b). The risk of crop damaging frost events has increased over the last 60 years across the winter cropping regions of Australia, despite there being an overall increase in average day temperatures (Zheng et al. 2015; Crimp et al. 2016).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This proposal aims to explore the option of genetic solutions to the ongoing challenge of canola frost damage in frost-prone production environments of Australia. This investment is to i) establish if there is sufficient diversity in canola at the reproductive frost tolerance stage of development and ii) develop a robust, reliable and consistent screening methodology.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/b7371025-74f9-4cbd-8a7b-3c52766d48f1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EOI - OSAKA - 2025: Australian Quantum Delegation to Expo 2025 Osaka</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/acd811a8-df64-4ecc-be48-a566fa99ace5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Industry, Science and Resources is seeking expressions of interest from Australian quantum technology companies to join a delegation to Expo 2025 Osaka in May.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/acd811a8-df64-4ecc-be48-a566fa99ace5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177210: NGN Integrated Disease Management and Disease Identification Workshops Northern Region</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/3c7c529c-bea6-4b2c-a8d8-9728609ef88b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Disease can pose a significant constraint on crop yield due to misdiagnosis and inappropriate disease response. Effective disease management strategies require accurately identifying the disease through visual symptoms or laboratory diagnosis; however, misdiagnosis of disease is common due to symptoms often being confused with other diseases or abiotic stresses. At an NGN forum in Bellata, growers raised concerns around disease identification and the need for better tools to assist with identification. In lieu of easily accessible and comprehensive tools for in-paddock identification of disease, there is an opportunity to upskill advisers in their own ability to identify disease symptoms. Furthermore, at an NGN forum in Thallon, growers raised interest in learning about management of diseases such as root lesion nematodes and crown rot through genetic resistance/tolerance. As single tactic management strategies may not always be effective, it is often necessary to take an integrated management approach, using a combination of tactics to ensure sufficient disease control.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through the delivery of workshops across GRDC’s Northern grains region, this investment will provide advisers with the practical knowledge, skills and resource materials to correctly identify disease and how to effectively manage disease using an integrated approach. Advisers will be better equipped to guide appropriate management decisions through correctly identifying crop disease symptoms and understanding the most effective set of management approaches available.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/3c7c529c-bea6-4b2c-a8d8-9728609ef88b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23CPU208: Clinical Services Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c1b94982-0641-4dab-9910-d22aec569e3b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market (ATM) is for the establishment of a Standing Offer Arrangement to stand up a Clinical Services Panel.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c1b94982-0641-4dab-9910-d22aec569e3b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NGA25 - 008: Heritage consultant to develop the conservation management plan (CMP) for the National Gallery of Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c32d0f1e-38a9-4cd1-a4e1-8d254513955d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Gallery of Australia (National Gallery) aims to engage a heritage consultant to prepare a Conservation Management Plan (CMP) providing a sound basis for the management of the built environment of the gallery building and its significant attributes, the conservation of the gallery building, the Australian gardens and the sculpture garden and its heritage significance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c32d0f1e-38a9-4cd1-a4e1-8d254513955d</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SWA-2025-A: 2025 Research Summit</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/57ea6e58-83ad-4321-ad54-230ac9ff2e82</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of Conference Management and Workshop Facilitation Services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/57ea6e58-83ad-4321-ad54-230ac9ff2e82</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09954: RAAF Richmond Refurbishment Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3b41e63d-3cbc-4ab0-a9bc-d24dbc7979aa</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RAAF Richmond Refurbishment Works, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3b41e63d-3cbc-4ab0-a9bc-d24dbc7979aa</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08249: HMAS Albatross Electrical Upgrades and Building Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/984f099e-bd78-4450-8c23-931bc2872d67</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Albatross Electrical Upgrades and Building Works, NSW&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/984f099e-bd78-4450-8c23-931bc2872d67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09953: Moorebank Military Area Building Refurbishment Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/be1de734-d9be-4114-ad67-f176a4093e60</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Moorebank Military Area Building Refurbishment Works, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/be1de734-d9be-4114-ad67-f176a4093e60</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E24-39492: Procurement of Fraud Case Management System (CMS)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/730b26c0-2410-47dd-9d69-f7fc70f1317f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health and Aged Care is seeking to procure a new off-the-shelf Fraud CMS to enhance its fraud management capabilities. The new CMS should ensure compliance with the Australian Government Investigations Standards (AGIS), improve efficiency, accuracy, and reporting capabilities, and streamline processes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/730b26c0-2410-47dd-9d69-f7fc70f1317f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E24-502095: Future Owner of National Workplace Initiative</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5d2c5390-d699-4bce-94ec-1897be051f05</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department is seeking submissions for a suitable qualified and experienced organisation take on the long-term ownership of and operating responsibility for the National Workplace Initiative (NWI). This will include taking over responsibility for continuous development and ongoing implementation of all four key elements of the NWI.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5d2c5390-d699-4bce-94ec-1897be051f05</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>027 - NMI - 2024/25: Procurement of an automated sample preparation platform capable of immunoaffinity purification</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/00b321b5-cb05-4171-a523-cf100a5a6e45</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Procurement of an automated sample preparation platform for the extraction of peptide hormones using magnetic bead immunoaffinity purification extraction protocols for the Australian Sports Drug Testing laboratory (ASDTL) of the Chemical &amp;amp; Biological Metrology Branch of the National Measurement Institute&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/00b321b5-cb05-4171-a523-cf100a5a6e45</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2147/RFT: Provision of Onshore Services for the Humanitarian Integration and Settlement Program (HISP)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e6b7e516-414a-400a-add6-67447259049e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Home Affairs is seeking Humanitarian Integration and Settlement Services for refugee and humanitarian clients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e6b7e516-414a-400a-add6-67447259049e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2170/RFT: Provision of Australian Cultural Orientation (AUSCO) Services for Humanitarian Integration and Settlement Program (HISP)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed1564a4-455c-4ef6-808e-d98afc49bc3a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Home Affairs is seeking Australian Cultural Orientation (AUSCO) program services for the Humanitarian Integration and Settlement Program (HISP).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed1564a4-455c-4ef6-808e-d98afc49bc3a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09920: Porton Barracks Minor Repair and Maintenance, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8acc6383-99e8-441c-9942-80bf5e5c9bda</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Porton Barracks Minor Repair and Maintenance Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8acc6383-99e8-441c-9942-80bf5e5c9bda</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NMP2125/RFI/001: DGMSS Autonomous Hull and Propeller Cleaning System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed1c8c8c-4ba3-4704-975c-6d87210ee40c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Navy is seeking innovative in-water autonomous hull and propeller cleaning technology.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed1c8c8c-4ba3-4704-975c-6d87210ee40c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>23/962-OT: Managed Service for Enterprise Data Platform (EDP)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/af7a39b6-22ab-4be7-b757-d614652c3c99</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Bank is seeking to source value-for-money Managed Service Contract for Enterprise Data Platform (EDP).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/af7a39b6-22ab-4be7-b757-d614652c3c99</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>085 - QCON - 2024/25: Questacon Replacement Two-Way Radio Fleet</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/34ea8ba0-af6b-4c34-93bd-95480062bdc8</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Request for Tender (RFT) is for the procurement of a fleet of 75 hand-held two-way radios, including any necessary firmware or hardware upgrades to existing radio repeaters.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/34ea8ba0-af6b-4c34-93bd-95480062bdc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AASB-2024-12: AASB Innovative Research Proposals</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/791544b3-8019-47de-bfa9-1b219d94f264</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reimagine reporting and inform the future of standard setting - Call for Research Proposals&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/791544b3-8019-47de-bfa9-1b219d94f264</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBP_CON_001: Provision of imported plasma and recombinant products</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/32c0c3a2-bbdb-4895-8422-8ce47ef831f3</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Blood Authority (NBA) invites Tenders for the provision of imported plasma and recombinant products, namely recombinant Factor VIII (rFVIII) and Factor IX (rFIX) products.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/32c0c3a2-bbdb-4895-8422-8ce47ef831f3</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_1294: Kibo - ABC</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f918bbe-86f6-4f99-b806-4446e3682ddb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Deliver Kibo - ABC initiatives on behalf of the Australian Space Agency to an Australian audience&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f918bbe-86f6-4f99-b806-4446e3682ddb</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49923-1: RFT for Collective and Individual Training Support Services (CITSS)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/689b263b-5bbb-49d1-b36d-6e823545d096</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Collective and Individual Training Support Services (CITSS) Standing Offer Panel&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/689b263b-5bbb-49d1-b36d-6e823545d096</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFAT-1051: Indonesia Economic Governance Investment</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b97bb436-82d3-488f-90e0-1da7f233eaf3</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Indonesia Economic Governance Investment&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b97bb436-82d3-488f-90e0-1da7f233eaf3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09296: HMAS Stirling Environmental Works, WA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7eb1cfc5-a2de-44f4-9a33-38032c73e19f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Stirling Environmental Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7eb1cfc5-a2de-44f4-9a33-38032c73e19f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPR202501: Provision for the end-to-end process design for the Basin Plan Review submissions process</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ca4a64c2-5919-43dd-a008-63236db5d531</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market (ATM) is for the provision of: Provision of end-to-end Process Design and Implantation Plan for the Basin Plan Review submissions process&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ca4a64c2-5919-43dd-a008-63236db5d531</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OPC-FRL-RFT-0125: Provision of Cloud Hosting and Other Related Services for the Federal Register of LegislationRL</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/010c896f-23c9-4fbe-af7a-332e6b81659a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Commonwealth of Australia, represented by the Office of the Parliamentary Counsel (OPC), requires the services of a suitably qualified and experienced contractor to provide cloud hosting services for the Federal Register of Legislation (the Register) website and provide other related services (the “Services”) as set out in this Statement of Work.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/010c896f-23c9-4fbe-af7a-332e6b81659a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFAS-25/26-WTP-ITR01: PFAS WATER TREATMENT PLANT ITR - JERVIS BAY RANGE FACILITY AND BANDIANA MILITARY AREA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ab114db1-f484-49c1-9ba4-6cace88590ff</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ITR - PFAS Water Treatment Plant (WTP) at Jervis Bay Range Facility (JBRF) and at Bandiana Military Area (BMA)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ab114db1-f484-49c1-9ba4-6cace88590ff</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT1001013682: Logistics Services for National Agent and Access Points</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ddc64bee-3e12-42bd-8018-42b2e0497e10</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the provision of Logistics Services for the National Agent and Access Points&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ddc64bee-3e12-42bd-8018-42b2e0497e10</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JLC/FCB/RFT/40281: National Supply and Distribution of ADF Petroleum, Oil and Lubricant (POL) Supplies</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2b4dfc3c-b3be-43c1-a0d3-5eaf76709e8d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;National Supply and Distribution of ADF Petroleum, Oil and Lubricant (POL) Supplies&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2b4dfc3c-b3be-43c1-a0d3-5eaf76709e8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08352: HMAS Waterhen South Wharf Mid Life Refit</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c4d0cd41-201b-4c9f-b48c-6d2b41ea41a7</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Waterhen South Wharf Mid Life Refit&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c4d0cd41-201b-4c9f-b48c-6d2b41ea41a7</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDBA-SRC000334: Hydraulic Models for Reviewing Rating Tables</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2ca16b17-9af9-4163-af51-d378b90bd6ae</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;MDBA has number for models and sub-models, event-based rainfall runoff modelling, for flood operations in the Upper Murray, Kiewa and Ovens. These models require suitably verified rating tables to ensure flood water level predictions are reasonably accurate, especially at the upper end of the rating tables where insufficient gauging exist.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2ca16b17-9af9-4163-af51-d378b90bd6ae</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MoAD-ATM-4889: Provision of 2D &amp; 3D Design Services for Press Gallery Exhibition</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1a578c04-9806-492f-98e3-ed8de60c1f2b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Museum of Australian Democracy (MoAD) requires exhibition design services, including 2D and 3D design to provide the experiential interpretation of the curatorial concepts and content, sufficient for the creation and construction of a new long-term exhibition, the House of Representatives Press Gallery Exhibition at Old Parliament House (OPH), Canberra. In particular, the interpretative design of storyline, themes, key messages, objects, mood and tone as described in the ‘Curatorial Brief’. Designers will be responsible for working collaboratively with the MoAD Curatorial, Exhibitions, Heritage and Digital teams and external creative consultants to develop concept designs through to fully documented 2D and 3D design and all accompanying schedules for construction, fabrication and production.&amp;nbsp; Services will also include the oversight of exhibition fabrication and graphic production and supervision of installation to ensure a successfully completed project, in conjunction with specialist staff of MoAD.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tenderers are invited to respond to either 2D or 3D design or both. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The 2D and 3D design packages will be considered independently.&amp;nbsp; In tendering both packages, tenderers may be offered one or both packages. Sub-contracting is permitted and should be noted in the response.&amp;nbsp; A Value for Money assessment will be made against the evaluation criteria.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1a578c04-9806-492f-98e3-ed8de60c1f2b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>D25/43474: EIA banning importation and use of asbestos in Lao PDR</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d2d073bb-85f2-43d8-be21-3d15ad4a3149</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To establish a Contract for An Economic Impact Assessment of banning importation and use of asbestos fibre and asbestos containing materials in Lao PDR&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d2d073bb-85f2-43d8-be21-3d15ad4a3149</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIMSRFT763: Asset Mapping and Maintenance Policy Development</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f9aef78e-4539-4d3c-886e-b7e5409aa17d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Institute of Marine Science (AIMS) requires an Asset and Maintenance Management contractor to carry out asset identification, asset mapping and maintenance policy document creation including safe work instructions to assist AIMS in managing its critical assets associated with the National Sea Simulation (SeaSim).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f9aef78e-4539-4d3c-886e-b7e5409aa17d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LSD/RFI/54755/1: Joint Project 8218 Theatre Logistics-Deployable Camp Infrastructure Sub-program</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/930d11b1-fb42-42d0-a1ac-2033c5fab192</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Joint Project 8218 Deployable Camp Infrastructure Market Sounding&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/930d11b1-fb42-42d0-a1ac-2033c5fab192</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25002: Warehousing and Logistics for Tourism Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/17b6dbbd-bcfd-44c1-9bf4-672c62f586ec</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Services for warehousing storage, pick and pack and global logistics for Tourism Australia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/17b6dbbd-bcfd-44c1-9bf4-672c62f586ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTA-RFT-61541: Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) Products and Service Solutions</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1e9710e5-dc52-4446-85d5-8ce8c484cc32</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The DTA is inviting all ERP providers to apply for Category 3 Enterprise Resource Planning Products and Service Solutions on the Software Marketplace and ERP panel.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1e9710e5-dc52-4446-85d5-8ce8c484cc32</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2024/3584: Repository Data Management and Delivery</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d86d1d93-e2e1-4525-bf10-6785a11df88a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoscience Australia is seeking comprehensive, innovative and cost-effective proposals to implement a modern, scalable and sustainable digital data management and storage solution to meet its evolving business requirements and objectives.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d86d1d93-e2e1-4525-bf10-6785a11df88a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11735: Delivery of Digital Health Standards Training and Education</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b642292a-70e6-4f98-b252-fb60ee41c7a2</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Through this RFT the Agency is seeking a supplier who can deliver digital health standards training, initially deliveringvirtual workshops for four FHIR courses that have been tailored to the Australian market. There are plans for delivery of additional FHIR courses and other digital health standards courses to support digital health standards adoption and implementation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b642292a-70e6-4f98-b252-fb60ee41c7a2</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPC-12139: Vulnerability Management System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/08a1b366-c180-4e6a-bb5c-ebbd20bbf595</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Taxation Office (ATO) is seeking the Provision of a Vulnerability Management System&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/08a1b366-c180-4e6a-bb5c-ebbd20bbf595</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT A24/41: Request for Tender for the Provision of ICT Managed Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7854b452-f732-46a8-b1ff-f1046dcc4885</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The NCA is seeking to implement a new arrangement with a partner to deliver ICT Managed Service to a high-quality service management capability.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7854b452-f732-46a8-b1ff-f1046dcc4885</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST07504: RAAF Glenbrook Infrastructure Replacement, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/327eabb8-2ef4-41e8-bc3b-cf2ea0a04b0b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RAAF Glenbrook Infrastructure Replacement Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/327eabb8-2ef4-41e8-bc3b-cf2ea0a04b0b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09927: HMAS Cerberus Multiple Building Works, VIC</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eb15e9c0-d221-4070-9077-b44ce0e835d5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Cerberus Multiple Building Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eb15e9c0-d221-4070-9077-b44ce0e835d5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ6575: PPIP-VAN-PVCPS Port Vila Central Police Station, George Pompidou, Vanuatu - Head Contractor (Design and Construct)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f3a78bfa-bb0c-461c-92d1-3a2c6e651c90</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Notice is for the purpose of informing Industry of the procurement for the services of Head Contractor (Design and Construct).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f3a78bfa-bb0c-461c-92d1-3a2c6e651c90</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A25/2: Commemoration of Marion Mahony Griffin and Walter Burely Griffin - Design and Construction Contractor</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0c9907cf-773b-464a-9a78-78671a43c746</link>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Marion Mahony Griffin and Walter Burley Griffin Commemoration - Design and Construction Contractor&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0c9907cf-773b-464a-9a78-78671a43c746</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2024_0930: Engagement of Interpretation, Translation and Interpreter Audio-Visual Enabling Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/20e9499b-d49a-42b1-b7e2-6a27ccf96b9f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of interpretation, translation and audio-visual enabling services to support international engagement.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/20e9499b-d49a-42b1-b7e2-6a27ccf96b9f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctic ATM24/5421: ATM 24/5421 Psychological (Adaptability) Assessments</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e727bb2f-a969-4257-9263-30ba86577887</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Establishment of a Deed of Standing Offer to provide Psychological (Adaptability) Assessments to the Australian Antarctic Division&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e727bb2f-a969-4257-9263-30ba86577887</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-2024-25-00662: Commercial Negotiation Training Course</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1dd6c459-2117-4e74-b499-096f8731cc93</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Finance is seeking to engage a suitably qualified supplier to develop and deliver a half-day training course on commercial negotiation relevant to the Commonwealth Procurement Framework, specifically targeted towards APS officials.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1dd6c459-2117-4e74-b499-096f8731cc93</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-5138: Request for Information on assessment tool(s) suitable for children to support NDIS reform initiatives</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/653b288d-eb27-4ded-a229-df9128ae35bb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Disability Insurance Agency is seeking submissions regarding available assessment tools for children that may be suitable for the NDIS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/653b288d-eb27-4ded-a229-df9128ae35bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-5137: Request for Information on targeted support needs assessment tool(s) to support NDIS reform initiatives</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9892eb56-7b97-4ebf-8818-06dd87e9a8dc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Disability Insurance Agency is seeking submissions regarding available assessment tools that assess needs for targeted disability supports funded under the NDIS.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9892eb56-7b97-4ebf-8818-06dd87e9a8dc</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-4807: Request for Tender for the provision of needs assessment tool(s) to support NDIS Reform Initiatives</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1242e7b7-8313-4313-bdbf-dee0205332d0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Disability Insurance Agency invites Tenders for the provision of needs assessment tool(s) suitable for people aged 16 years and over, including related operational support services and a system integration solution.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1242e7b7-8313-4313-bdbf-dee0205332d0</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Navy/TF/NSWT/40036: Navigation and Synthetic Warfare Training Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/417f25fb-e36f-47af-a4a3-f10445dc9eb5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Navigation and Synthetic Warfare Training Services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/417f25fb-e36f-47af-a4a3-f10445dc9eb5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPC-12826: Real-Time Fraud Risk Engine</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/82a2b0cd-682f-4f96-8072-ec937e4897db</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ATO is approaching the open market to procure&amp;nbsp;an industry-leading, innovative real-time fraud risk engine to strengthen ATO digital systems and controls.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/82a2b0cd-682f-4f96-8072-ec937e4897db</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177223: NGN Chickpea time of sowing for disease control in Southern Queensland</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/297c08ef-46fc-4ebc-a24d-151cbb3b3038</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Chickpeas are an important part of winter crop rotations in Queensland; however, disease can be a major limitation to production. Ascochyta blight is a major disease of chickpea, for which current varieties lack resistance to. Fungicides are the primary method of controlling Ascochyta blight, often requiring multiple applications when conditions are conductive. The high cost of these applications and potential for the development of fungicide resistance means alternative control methods are needed. Using an integrated disease management strategy can improve disease control and limit the risks of developing resistance. Optimising the time of sowing can be an effective method to manage Ascochyta blight as later plantings can help to avoid disease impacts through limiting the number of rain events.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/297c08ef-46fc-4ebc-a24d-151cbb3b3038</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177215: NGN Faba bean variety and agronomy trials in Tasmania</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/8a9f4a4f-6613-4bf6-8f9e-1aa0fd897862</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The NGN faba bean variety and agronomy trials in Tasmania aim to address the current limitations in faba bean production within the region. Despite the high cost of importing new varieties and the limited adoption of faba beans due to lower returns compared to other field crops, there is a renewed interest in this legume rotation crop. This resurgence is driven by the development of local market opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/8a9f4a4f-6613-4bf6-8f9e-1aa0fd897862</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025021: CSIRORFT2025021 Café Services - CSIRO Hobart</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/026780da-efe7-4817-a801-2e8a63210c6b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSIRO through this Request for Tender (RFT) is seeking responses from suitably qualified and experienced service providers for the provision of café style food and beverage services (Services) for the café located at CSIRO Hobart, Tasmania.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/026780da-efe7-4817-a801-2e8a63210c6b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025015: Boolardy Homestead Airstrip upgrade project, Murchison WA – Head Contractor Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3ca6a01e-039d-41e3-a9b6-017f7bec84b9</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSIRO through this RFT is seeking responses from suitably qualified and experienced service providers for the provision of Head Contractor (Contractor) construction services for the delivery of the Boolardy Homestead airstrip upgrade project located at Inyarrimanha Ilgari Bundara, the CSIRO Murchison Radio-astronomy Observatory (the Observatory), Beringarra Pindar Road, Murchison WA 6603.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The scope of the project includes, but is not limited to the following:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(a) Heritage protection as required&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(b) Clearing and grubbing activities for the project&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(c) Cut/fill enabling earthworks including erosion, sediment and stormwater control&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(d) Extension of current airstrip pavement to 1500m in length and 23m in width&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(e) Re-grade and seal of airstrip with tie-in cross-strip (runway2)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(f) New sealed taxi-way and parking apron&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(g) Marking of sealed airstrip, taxi-way and parking apron&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(h) Amend and match existing fencing&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(i) Floodlighting&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(j) Relocation of departure lounge (a demountable) and an existing Illuminated Wind Direction Indicator&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(k) Potential (cost dependant) new fencing, vehicle and pedestrian gates.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3ca6a01e-039d-41e3-a9b6-017f7bec84b9</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2023-24RFQ002: Scoping Reviews for older adults and diet and sustainability to inform the revision of the Australian Dietary Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fef7ec2e-3867-4c27-8b53-fe0209da9826</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Services to conduct scoping reviews for older adults and diet and sustainability to inform the revision the Australian Dietary Guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fef7ec2e-3867-4c27-8b53-fe0209da9826</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10028704: Airport Building Control Services for Federally Leased Airports</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/55060c68-abf4-43fc-8cce-b684abc05ce3</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The department seeks to procure Airport Building Control services at 20 federally leased airports to administer and advise airport lessees and operators on the building control requirements outlined under the &lt;em&gt;Airports Act 1996&lt;/em&gt; and the Airports (Building Control) Regulations 1996.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/55060c68-abf4-43fc-8cce-b684abc05ce3</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 2024-25 03: National Arts and Disability Forums and Gatherings</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/58e7a063-0ad7-4ead-9ef3-ee1631368c91</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Australia is the Australian Government’s principal arts investment and advisory body. We are currently seeking tenders from a suitably qualified individual, organisation or consortium to develop, deliver and evaluate a series of National Arts and Disability forums and gatherings from 2025 to 2028&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/58e7a063-0ad7-4ead-9ef3-ee1631368c91</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 2024-25 02: National Arts and Disability Code of Practice or Guidelines</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/f05c0f60-98e9-4995-8532-c6e0110b1241</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Australia is the Australian Government’s principal arts investment and advisory body.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We are currently seeking tenders from a suitably qualified individual, organisation or consortium to consult with the arts, screen, games and cultural sector, and to develop and steward a new National Arts and Disability Code of Practice or appropriate Guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/f05c0f60-98e9-4995-8532-c6e0110b1241</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10514: Lismore Remediation &amp; Refurbishment Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/06168fd5-166d-46f3-b8df-7411e12c2728</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Lismore Remediation &amp;amp; Refurbishment Works, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/06168fd5-166d-46f3-b8df-7411e12c2728</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proc-84380: DHA Upgrade-Wattle Grove NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1741a1b8-d267-4ca8-80a1-44d3cf38b178</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of Upgrage for Wattle Grove, NSW -&amp;nbsp; DHA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1741a1b8-d267-4ca8-80a1-44d3cf38b178</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPSRD/RFI 001: Request for Information for Industry Technical Capability in Nuclear Regulation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dd308ca9-4f95-4cbc-a5e1-9c49cfb8be08</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Request for Information for Industry Technical Capability in Nuclear Regulation&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dd308ca9-4f95-4cbc-a5e1-9c49cfb8be08</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2163/RFT: Provision of Maintenance and Repair of Navigational Aids and Moorings</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9b3b6866-209a-4e38-8970-bba89ab96274</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Border Force (ABF) is seeking a Service Provider for the provision of maintenance and repair of navigational aids and moorings at Ashmore Reef and Christmas Island.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9b3b6866-209a-4e38-8970-bba89ab96274</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ADSS/NOT/52004/1: Support to Space Domain Awareness (SDA) Capabilities</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/40b4fd8a-b5a4-41be-b5d7-218fe9db0bde</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Advance notice - invitation to register to Support SDA Capabilities at Exmouth ,WA and Edinburgh, SA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/40b4fd8a-b5a4-41be-b5d7-218fe9db0bde</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESE25/7095: Request for Information in relation to Department of Employment and Workplace Relations Health Insurance</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/40f0e5a7-2379-4741-af39-cd8e4e6ad4bb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Department of Employment and Workplace Relations Health Insurance REOI&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/40f0e5a7-2379-4741-af39-cd8e4e6ad4bb</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E24-312865: REQUEST FOR TENDER FOR THE PROVISION OF CLINICAL QUALITY REGISTRY SERVICES STREAM 1- ROUND 2 OF THE NATIONAL CQR PROGRAM</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7e61acde-5764-4bb1-b406-c0440b581ca0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Stream 1 of the National Clinical Quality Registry Program (Round 2)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7e61acde-5764-4bb1-b406-c0440b581ca0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PMSP-2022-0003-01-1: Pacific Maritime Security Program Acquisition of Enhanced Aerial Surveillance Services (Fixed-Wing)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fc3a3478-b243-4757-bbd9-79e0a55c6f5c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PMSP Acquisition of Enhanced Aerial Surveillance Services (Fixed-Wing)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fc3a3478-b243-4757-bbd9-79e0a55c6f5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JASD/NOT/20200/6: Defence Search and Rescue Services Contract</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/42f312b4-dfa2-4718-87ab-65112e219370</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Notice to industry regarding the upcoming Defence Search and Rescue Services (DSARS) RFT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/42f312b4-dfa2-4718-87ab-65112e219370</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM 24/3610: ATM 24/3610 Antarctic Helicopter Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e3d1f8bf-6951-402b-a75c-52ecf6b7b58c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Antarctic Aviation Helicopter Services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e3d1f8bf-6951-402b-a75c-52ecf6b7b58c</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>55737: SEG-ESD-DSCS-E-Multi-Sites</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/31296a96-2696-4028-b9ed-4ac94be0ffb2</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Procurement of Electricity to Defence Sites in NSW, ACT, VIC, TAS and SA for up to 5 years&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/31296a96-2696-4028-b9ed-4ac94be0ffb2</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E24-581412_RF: RFT for services to distribute Pharmaceutical Benefits Scheme (PBS) medicines under Community Service Obligation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c6fa6e29-5bb7-4707-9fa6-e4ec34383b69</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market seeks to procure the services of organisation/s for the distribution of Pharmaceutical Benefit Scheme (PBS) medicines to community pharmacies across Australia. Distribution must be conducted in accordance with the Community Service Obligation (CSO) Compliance Requirements and Service Standards. Services are also required to support the prevention and management of onshore medicine shortages. Successful organisation/s will be subsidised for the additional costs required to meet these conditions through a fixed annual funding pool.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c6fa6e29-5bb7-4707-9fa6-e4ec34383b69</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFP-48897: Pacific Maritime Security Program - Pacific Maritime Support Coordinator</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0c06c63a-e041-4092-9ab4-beccb6f4cfa6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of maintenance and support services for Guardian Class boats and other vessels&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0c06c63a-e041-4092-9ab4-beccb6f4cfa6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DemoATM2025: Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGF_17: Supply of Medical Grade Footwear to eligible persons</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NOTE: existing suppliers need not reapply&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Medical Grade Footwear (MGF) Programme is an important part of DVA’s health care arrangements and is part of the Rehabilitation Appliance Programme (RAP).&amp;nbsp; The MGF Programme provides a nation-wide access to a wide range of MGF and related services for entitled persons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPC-2017: Invitation to provide Day Procedure Centre Services to the Veteran Community</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Veterans’ Affairs (DVA) is seeking to contract with eligible stand-alone private day hospitals (referred to as Day Procedure Centres or DPCs) to provide DPC services for DVA Entitled Persons across Australia from 1 October 2017 onwards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHS-16: Private Hospital Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DVA is seeking the provision of Private Hospital services for Entitled Persons by publishing this &lt;em&gt;Invitation to Provide Private Hospital Services to the Veteran Community&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNS16: Department of Veterans' Affairs Community Nursing Services Invitation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Department of Veterans' Affairs invites interested suppliers of Community Nursing Services to apply to provide these services from 1 July 2016.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>