<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://www.tenders.gov.au#rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>AusTender Current ATM List</title>
    <language>en-AU</language>
    <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/List</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:35:05 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <description>AusTender Current ATM List</description>
    <item>
      <title>AARC-ARS-03-2025: Intention to Register - Army Research Scheme-Research Network</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b092e14c-004e-4e21-af57-540f78409de5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ITR-AARC-Research Network&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b092e14c-004e-4e21-af57-540f78409de5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NDIA PROC 6195: Specialist Disability Supports- Assessments</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4f64c73d-ecaa-46b9-9dbd-a817a7e9fea8</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Specialist Disability Supports- Assessments&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4f64c73d-ecaa-46b9-9dbd-a817a7e9fea8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST02060-ECI HC_CB: EST02060-GIDP- Withdrawal Notice - Chowder ECI HC - Notice of Potential Upcoming Procurement</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9d3217a2-d09d-475b-9a07-5d61deeabd98</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;AusTender Withdrawal of Upcoming Procurement&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This notice is for the purposes of informing industry that Defence is withdrawing EST02060-GIDP-Chowder Bay Early Contractor Involvement Head Contract - Notice of Potential Upcoming Procurement, published on AusTender on 18&amp;nbsp;July&amp;nbsp;2025. It is still the Commonwealth’s intention to procure a works contractor for works at Chowder Bay under the Project. However, the timing and engagement model of any future procurement related to the Project is being further considered by the Commonwealth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9d3217a2-d09d-475b-9a07-5d61deeabd98</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EWPNOTICE 01/2025: Notice - Estate Works Program Defence Industry Update</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c0a087cf-70b1-4fca-9ccd-826c13f47b07</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Notice - Estate Work Program - Industry information update published on Defence Internet&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c0a087cf-70b1-4fca-9ccd-826c13f47b07</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPS26000037: SDI to IP Backbone</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6b9a873d-8062-4b7e-8ef5-97b7cfbb0c87</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Internet Protocol (IP) TV Solution- Internet Protocol (IP) TV solution, including 3-5 years of support and maintenance.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6b9a873d-8062-4b7e-8ef5-97b7cfbb0c87</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GYMPIE QLD RFI: LONG TERM COMMONWEALTH LEASE GYMPIE, QLD AND SURROUNDING AREAS</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ae47cf8d-3a72-4518-9c33-cfbbd2f52d17</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exceptional Leasing Opportunity COMMONWEALTH LEASE GYMPIE, QLD AND SURROUNDING AREAS&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ae47cf8d-3a72-4518-9c33-cfbbd2f52d17</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10824: Darling Downs Demolition Works, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0066d73d-2af7-4a8e-aa42-a4384906b6ec</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Darling Downs Demolition Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0066d73d-2af7-4a8e-aa42-a4384906b6ec</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASCA-PITCHDAY-25: ASCA Pitch Day 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/418c2be7-661c-4b76-a801-4ccc6ed588bc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Open Request for Information for Pitches to be presented at ASCA's Pitch Day 2025.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/418c2be7-661c-4b76-a801-4ccc6ed588bc</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT12471: Provision of Accessibility and Toolset</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/74aaa9b2-9575-4294-89ba-525bc9082f1c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Agency requires an Accessibility Tool testing service to support a consistent accessibility testing approach across a suite of Agency owned products.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/74aaa9b2-9575-4294-89ba-525bc9082f1c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPS26000003: Chamber Audio Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/768e5b3a-3eba-47a2-bc7a-927087dd0f08</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DPS invites Tenders for the provision of Chamber Audio system and associated services, in accordance with this Request for Tender (RFT).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/768e5b3a-3eba-47a2-bc7a-927087dd0f08</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MDBA EEWD PM: Resourcing Support for Project Delivery</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b91c37fc-1b9e-4da8-807b-22bba90c311a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To establish Contract for Establish Contract for Resourcing Support for Project Delivery&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b91c37fc-1b9e-4da8-807b-22bba90c311a</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25191: Tourism Australia - ATE27-31 Exhibition Management Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/53dfb15b-65a0-41a2-a496-07988570b1fc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tourism Australia - ATE27-31 Exhibition Management Services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/53dfb15b-65a0-41a2-a496-07988570b1fc</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Braidwood EOI: Access Point services Braidwood</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/624aae9c-1eae-4589-bef5-89b91bfe5457</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Government agency Services Australia is seeking Expressions of Interest from organisations to provide agent service.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/624aae9c-1eae-4589-bef5-89b91bfe5457</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177301: Optimisation of crop establishment: Procurement A – Researching novel approaches to achieve a step change in crop establ</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/73a16821-ba98-4536-bc4f-5fd2131085da</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Optimisation of crop establishment: Procurement A - Researching novel approaches to achieve a step change in crop establishment for Australian grain growers&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/73a16821-ba98-4536-bc4f-5fd2131085da</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GRIFFITH NSW EOI: LONG TERM COMMONWEALTH LEASE GRIFFITH, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9df2c820-6053-4ffc-ba69-a5b844de6d01</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Exceptional Leasing Opportunity COMMONWEALTH LEASE&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;GRIFFITH AND SURROUNDS, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9df2c820-6053-4ffc-ba69-a5b844de6d01</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFAT-1059: Philippines Procurement Administrative and Logistics Management Support Services Phase 2 (PALMSS)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/57298784-0a55-4bd8-bb8f-042cf1add476</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Philippines Procurement, Administrative and Logistics Management Support Services (PALMSS)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/57298784-0a55-4bd8-bb8f-042cf1add476</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025032: Cafe Services CSIRO Marsfield</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/447ca554-ef87-4423-9d68-53fd8870d181</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSIRO through this Request for Tender (RFT) is seeking responses from suitably qualified and experienced service providers for the provision of café style food and beverage services (Services) for the café located at CSIRO Marsfield, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/447ca554-ef87-4423-9d68-53fd8870d181</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025/1428: First Nations Advisory Group for Geoscience Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aacf5c75-4f08-4b2d-adc2-f088942414f5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market (ATM) is for the provision of a First Nations Advisory Group to provide Geoscience Australia (GA) with culturally informed and non-binding strategic advice and/or recommendations to support the delivery of local and national activities and initiatives.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aacf5c75-4f08-4b2d-adc2-f088942414f5</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ET/PMB/CBR/2025/01: RFP - Provide Leased Office Accommodation in the ACT</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/86974572-263b-41f4-98c6-2036bb85148d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RFP -&amp;nbsp; Provide Leased Office Accommodation in the ACT&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/86974572-263b-41f4-98c6-2036bb85148d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESE25/9260: Office for Youth Mental Health and Psychological Program Support</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eafe73bb-f571-4245-94d0-547a7ac1d626</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Request for Quotation (RFQ) seeks an AHPRA-qualified supplier to provide psychological and mental health support during virtual and in-person meetings for the Office for Youth's Youth Engagement Programs. The service period will be from 1 December 2025 to 30 June 2026.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eafe73bb-f571-4245-94d0-547a7ac1d626</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NGA25-102: POS, Inventory Management System and E-Commerce Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7ace8871-4363-46ec-8df9-8f63cfc03c29</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Gallery Australia is seeking information from industry providers regarding integrated point of sale, inventory management systems and e-commerce platforms to unify our retail operations. This request for information (RFI) is issued to gain an understanding of current market capabilities and innovative approaches that support multiuser, SaaS systems within the retail framework for the National Gallery’s Art Store.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7ace8871-4363-46ec-8df9-8f63cfc03c29</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFI 14-2025 Notice 3: National Police Check Systems Replacement (NPCSR) Project - Supplementary Industry Notice 2</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cd88f453-eb25-42f1-9382-78c80eef2df2</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;National Police Check Systems Replacement (NPCSR) Project&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cd88f453-eb25-42f1-9382-78c80eef2df2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10728: RAAF Amberley Building Refurbishment, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d51a71cc-4242-45bc-8ba8-a3e7f86a9ed5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RAAF Amberley Building Refurbishment&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d51a71cc-4242-45bc-8ba8-a3e7f86a9ed5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSD/RFP/66367/1: Army Littoral System of Personal Flotation Devices (ALSPFD)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ef13c7de-3d2c-43e4-b9dd-95b603e70d08</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Request for Proposal (RFP) for a suite of Personal Flotation Devices (PFDs) to meet the emerging littoral capability&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ef13c7de-3d2c-43e4-b9dd-95b603e70d08</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177278: EOI: The Functional Sorghum Collective (FSC) - increasing the domestic demand for sorghum in the food/beverage sector</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/23764eed-f32d-4f8c-90e7-f48ec719425e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Functional Sorghum Collective (FSC) - increasing the domestic demand for sorghum in the food/beverage sector&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/23764eed-f32d-4f8c-90e7-f48ec719425e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177274: Development of next-generation breeding technologies</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/b7bb8d4a-4db4-4edd-bd6f-9bf96b98fcab</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This investment aims to develop the know-how and technical platforms required to deliver New Breeding Technologies (NBTs) for the Australian Grains Industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;New breeding technologies including gene editing, targeted mutagenesis, transformation and cisgenics are genome engineering tools with the potential to accelerate genetic gain in plant breeding programs. This in-turn provides opportunities to deliver improved outcomes for Australian grain growers through development of more sustainable, resilient and profitable crops. The Grains Research and Development Corporation (GRDC) has established the Accelerating Genetic Gain Strategic Initiative to drive the implementation of NBTs. This investment is supporting new collaborations between researchers, end-users and commercial entities to improve uptake of pre-breeding research outputs, create new paths-to-market and ensure grower adoption of new genetics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Through global engagement, several priority areas have been identified and GRDC is now seeking a response to the following open Tender.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Theme B: Creating and using genetic diversity&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Priority Area B.1: Development of next generation breeding technologies&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summary of the opportunity: A suite of tools including targeted mutagenesis, gene editing, transformation and cisgenics are widely deployed in pre-breeding research. The challenge now, is how to adopt such research-scale technologies in a breeding context so that outcomes benefit Australian growers. Approaches which address both technical challenges and licencing needs by bringing together traditional and non-traditional partners, Australian and International organisations, public and private entities will be required for success. In the first instance, a focus on key trait(s) with a strong value proposition for Australian grain producers will be required to demonstrate the value and path-to-market opportunity for next generation breeding technologies.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plant SynBio Australia Collaboration Opportunities&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Plant SynBio Australia (PSBA) was established through a 'Step Change' investment by the Commonwealth under the National Collaborative Research Infrastructure Strategy (NCRIS), managed by Bioplatforms Australia (BPA). It comprises a national network of facilities that provide plant synthetic biology infrastructure and expertise to academic, government, and industry users. Capabilities such as plant gene editing, transformation, and genetic technology development are offered through fee-for-service, research hotel, and collaborative engagement models. GRDC supports the engagement of tenderers with BPA for access to, and partnerships with, these facilities, enabling researchers and industry to generate knowledge and apply plant synthetic biology to deliver agricultural solutions. For more information, contact Dr Darren Plett at dplett@bioplatforms.com or visit https://bioplatforms.com/synthetic-biology/.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Applicants must be able to demonstrate freedom to operate and strict stewardship protocols for the new breeding technologies in target crops; wheat and/or barley. GRDC is seeking a 50:50 co-investment for this contract, please refer to the GRDC budget template (https://grdc.com.au/research/partnering-in-rde-investment/other-resources) for definitions of cash and in-kind contributions. GRDC investment will be up to AUD$5.8M over 4.5yrs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/b7bb8d4a-4db4-4edd-bd6f-9bf96b98fcab</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 62874: RFT 62874 Supply of Gymnasium (Physical Fitness) Equipment Standing Offer Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3d255b76-471d-4b5e-ae18-1f0f8c692c1f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Request for Tender for the Supply of Gymnasium (Physical Fitness) Equipment Standing Offer Panel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3d255b76-471d-4b5e-ae18-1f0f8c692c1f</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPC-14400: Provision of AI Coding Assistant Tool</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/613a99d7-e3f7-4425-9718-14ef252e7d92</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Taxation Office (ATO) is planning to incorporate new and current technologies to help support the ATO developer experience, by integrating AI coding assistant tools into the development workflow.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ATO is seeking to acquire an AI coding assistant tool to assist the ATO developers with more efficient code development to solve common programming issues which in turn gives developers more time to focus on higher value work, such as test case planning, security controls for application development and maintain current technologies for all developers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/613a99d7-e3f7-4425-9718-14ef252e7d92</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09942: HMAS Cerberus Building Refurbishments, VIC</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a144c6d4-4fee-462b-ab53-98d6be7a62f6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Cerberus Building Refurbishments, VIC&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a144c6d4-4fee-462b-ab53-98d6be7a62f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LC4 IS and T Summit: LC4 IS&amp;T Summit 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f645e813-5969-47fa-a58d-0bb4abd00d4a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LC4 IS&amp;amp;T Summit 02-03 October 2025&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f645e813-5969-47fa-a58d-0bb4abd00d4a</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-2024-25-00171: Industry Consultation: Whole of Australian Government (WoAG) GovCMS Drupal and Digital Experience Platform (DXP) Service</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2f3302fd-ec71-4c23-bd91-e7aea473146e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Web Development industry suppliers are invited to provide feedback on the current Department of Finance Whole of Australian Government (WoAG) GovCMS Drupal and Digital Experience Platform (DXP) Services Panel Arrangement Head Agreement and a draft Statement of Works.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2f3302fd-ec71-4c23-bd91-e7aea473146e</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>26000167: APH Clock Maintenance (RFI)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/489cd253-6a31-479a-b230-fdb9a55ec8a9</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Parliamentary Services is seeking information about the availability of clock bodies and mechanisms to provide spares to maintain the existing fleet of clocks throughout Australian Parliament House in Canberra Australia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/489cd253-6a31-479a-b230-fdb9a55ec8a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A25/017: National Carillon Instrument maintenance</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/565fefd1-215b-4134-aee9-22f23d7543a1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a procurement for regular maintenance services of the National Carillon instrument.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/565fefd1-215b-4134-aee9-22f23d7543a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPC-13439: Online Survey Platform</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b96f0e0b-1871-4495-95ff-7c75aed5da22</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ATO is seeking a comprehensive and holistic online survey platform&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b96f0e0b-1871-4495-95ff-7c75aed5da22</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08644: HMAS Stirling Training Centre Refurbishments, WA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c8a24357-98ab-424d-b103-23bf449ed8f6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Stirling Training Centre Refurbishment works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c8a24357-98ab-424d-b103-23bf449ed8f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09943: Shoalwater Bay Training Area Bushfire Safety Works, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eda7471c-5706-45ec-9435-b7a2af018401</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shoalwater Bay Training Area Bushfire Safety Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/eda7471c-5706-45ec-9435-b7a2af018401</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025/2458: Palynology for Greater McArthur Basin</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/62e41db4-a952-4783-913d-658d9916e98f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoscience Australia (GA), as part of the Birrindudu Deep Dive (BDD) project, is conducting a palynology feasibility study of the Greater McArthur Basin to determine whether a regional biostratigraphic framework can be developed for Proterozoic-aged strata across northern Australia. Quantitative palynological data will be acquired from legacy drillholes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/62e41db4-a952-4783-913d-658d9916e98f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AWM001485: Security Guarding Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e5356ae5-889e-4a2d-b883-5c334860da0d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Security Guarding Services for the Australian War Memorial&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e5356ae5-889e-4a2d-b883-5c334860da0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177275: New technologies for targeted recombination in breeding programs</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/95c4e966-a73a-4413-a9a1-e67c55fd6bc8</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Emerging technologies enabling targeted recombination in plants can accelerate genetic gain by reducing linkage drag, promoting rare events and generating novel diversity. This AU$4.5M investment supports method development and demonstration in key crops and traits. Proposals should show market potential and encourage collaboration across sectors, including international and Australian partners.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/95c4e966-a73a-4413-a9a1-e67c55fd6bc8</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177316: Australian Grains Industry Supply Chain Harmonisation Review</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/a585c75f-dfb6-4418-9f49-82cbb1cffe9e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To provide a review for GRDC of the Australian grains industry supply chain with recommendations for improvement in how information is extended for use in sustainability and traceability credentials. This includes consideration of sustainability credentials, emissions hotspots, and the capacity of growers and industry participants to meet evolving market requirements. The review will be supported by the development of case studies that reflect diverse supply chain configurations and illustrate key challenges and opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/a585c75f-dfb6-4418-9f49-82cbb1cffe9e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09300: Fort Gellibrand Refurbishments, VIC</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/05790cb0-b95b-44fc-8260-48a6c89a98a1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Fort Gellibrand Refurbishments&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/05790cb0-b95b-44fc-8260-48a6c89a98a1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2184/RFT: End User Services (EUS)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ff358a6-5ec7-4954-9374-5f07a5d98245</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;End User Services arrangement will provide the Department with the following sets of services:&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Workplace Support&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Service Management Support&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Service Desk&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; Secret ICT Support&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ff358a6-5ec7-4954-9374-5f07a5d98245</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 12272: Application Support and Maintenance Services for Digital Health Infrastructure</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8cd56555-0c07-4107-9845-e09d7e4c7e43</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Application Support and Maintenance (ASM) Services for Digital Health Infrastructure incl. My Health Record.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Agency is seeking tenders for the provision of Application Support and Maintenance Services for Digital Health Infrastructure which includes My Health Record.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8cd56555-0c07-4107-9845-e09d7e4c7e43</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVY/TF/ECM/58636: Extended Care Medic Higher Education Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/73a4785a-b5a0-4728-ac73-489d332bbc32</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Extended Care Medic Higher Education Services&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/73a4785a-b5a0-4728-ac73-489d332bbc32</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09280: Singleton Asbestos and Civil Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1434bc67-fd4b-4ca1-9d59-f3c085080cbf</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Singleton Asbestos and Civil Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1434bc67-fd4b-4ca1-9d59-f3c085080cbf</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10735: Tamworth GRES (General Reserves) Refurbishment and Upgrades, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1f4394a6-8576-4c3e-bfe1-d43606558469</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tamworth GRES (General Reserves) Refurbishment and Upgrade Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1f4394a6-8576-4c3e-bfe1-d43606558469</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>349a-2020-21-CU: Radar Modernisation Program - Confidentiality Undertaking</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/58e88541-c772-42e4-8f9d-f0a47bc10210</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Bureau of Meteorology (the Bureau) is seeking to procure the Radar Solution, which comprises several categories of radars to replace, upgrade or enhance its current fleet and the provision of other associated services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/58e88541-c772-42e4-8f9d-f0a47bc10210</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-2024-25-00870: Provision of Corporate Uniform - COMCAR</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89ca9e80-d40e-40b2-a7b9-4d1bb85b3c05</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of Corporate Uniform for COMCAR Driving and Administrative workforce&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89ca9e80-d40e-40b2-a7b9-4d1bb85b3c05</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSD/RFT/64473/1: Counter Small Uncrewed Aerial Systems Service Standing Offer Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b0574bfe-4cab-445f-be86-1134f4affc8d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Commonwealth requires services to support Counter small Uncrewed Aerial Systems (CsUAS) solutions across a range of Department of Defence (Defence) and other Whole of Government (WoG) sites.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b0574bfe-4cab-445f-be86-1134f4affc8d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OTA C2526-025: Provision of a professional conference organiser (PCO) for the 2026 Donation Symposium</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f98ba2a9-fb4d-4d0c-aa29-f9c30ce59a95</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of a professional conference organiser (PCO) for the 2026 Donation Symposium&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/f98ba2a9-fb4d-4d0c-aa29-f9c30ce59a95</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10732: Defence Science Technology Group Edinburgh Building Refurbishment, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/91898d02-33a5-476a-9d86-eb7354df2816</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence Science Technology Group Edinburgh Building Refurbishment Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/91898d02-33a5-476a-9d86-eb7354df2816</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_4808: COP31 Event Manager Contractor</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a2a8c8cd-6211-49b9-94de-aa20e073a6a3</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department is seeking Expressions of Interest (EOIs) from suitably experienced, qualified, and resourced respondents, who have the capability and capacity to deliver Event Management Contractor (EMC) services (Services) and who would be interested in responding to a future request for tender should Australia’s bid to host COP31 be confirmed.&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a2a8c8cd-6211-49b9-94de-aa20e073a6a3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025026: IT Infrastructure Hardware, Software and Services eProcurement Portal</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5f5571cb-5f76-4636-b65e-ed8884d1040b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;IT Infrastructure Hardware, Software and Services eProcurement Portal&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5f5571cb-5f76-4636-b65e-ed8884d1040b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>49923-2: Notification of Delay for Collective and Individual Training Support Services (CITSS) Panel Procurement</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b2a857e-4328-43d8-bb47-aff5966a2524</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CITSS Notification of Delay&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b2a857e-4328-43d8-bb47-aff5966a2524</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 May 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-2024-25-00990: Notice for the Whole of Australian Government - Campaign Evaluation Services Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/783330e0-834b-4ff5-b4a0-dad62843abd7</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Notice&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;for the Whole of Australian Government - Campaign Evaluation Services Arrangement&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/783330e0-834b-4ff5-b4a0-dad62843abd7</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09299: Palmer Barracks Buildings &amp; Civil Works, WA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e872f219-3b0a-4902-9698-047ca2dc8acb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Palmer Barracks Buildings &amp;amp; Civil Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e872f219-3b0a-4902-9698-047ca2dc8acb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NGA-091: Audio Guide Request for Information</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1021eb8f-7a9e-46c9-bdd5-329cd35ff987</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Gallery of Australia (the Gallery) is requesting information to evaluate options for a new audio guide platform for onsite, on tour and online visitors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1021eb8f-7a9e-46c9-bdd5-329cd35ff987</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NGA24-099: Carpark Management System Upgrade</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e17ebdd0-1b6c-48b9-8d5e-a142d11a9326</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Carpark Management System Upgrade&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e17ebdd0-1b6c-48b9-8d5e-a142d11a9326</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2185/RFT: Community Refugee Integration and Settlement Program</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ff903b93-4e2f-462c-a5f9-adc8468419ab</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The community Refugee Integration and Settlement Program (CRISP) allows Australian communities to sponsor and welcome refugee families to Australia. This Program, enables local groups to provide practical and financial support to refugees, helping them settle into new homes and communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ff903b93-4e2f-462c-a5f9-adc8468419ab</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09335: Port Wakefield General Building &amp; Road Works, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/52fcc784-025e-4da2-8ed9-a89dc9e02dc0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Port Wakefield General Building &amp;amp; Road Works, SA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/52fcc784-025e-4da2-8ed9-a89dc9e02dc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FIN-25-Metering-RFT: Electricity Metering Services Arrangement</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4aa5f1e6-a88e-4910-8aba-14e490ce5a02</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Electricity Metering Services Arrangement&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4aa5f1e6-a88e-4910-8aba-14e490ce5a02</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WS2384921345: RFT For the Provision of a Noise and Flight Path Monitoring Service</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a8b2c0f3-d858-4d4e-9ac5-c4ccbddb58c0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of a Noise and Flight Path Monitoring Service, as more fully described in the Statement of Requirements (SOR).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a8b2c0f3-d858-4d4e-9ac5-c4ccbddb58c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10847: Gallipoli Barracks Demountable Works, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/24cfee0f-8706-479e-bb83-61684c552388</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gallipoli Barracks Demountable Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/24cfee0f-8706-479e-bb83-61684c552388</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>66866: Transportable Superconducting Nanowire Single-Photon Detection System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b5550485-1e7e-4ea2-9ee4-98cc39411ca0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence is seeking to procure a transportable (&amp;lt;22 U) superconducting nanowire single-photon detection system.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b5550485-1e7e-4ea2-9ee4-98cc39411ca0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25214: Learning Management System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6fff9b41-b804-4ec9-bc2d-92adca8d6ff1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To find a suitable vendor to promote a Leaning Management System (LMS)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6fff9b41-b804-4ec9-bc2d-92adca8d6ff1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25186: Content Management System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ee3968f7-56a0-4576-aa27-4475d4920a7a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Content Management System&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ee3968f7-56a0-4576-aa27-4475d4920a7a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177323: Technical innovation to advance OH&amp;S in the Grains Industry</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/b16cd77e-d5b5-4186-804a-5b828794f8eb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This investment seeks to enhance safety across the grains industry by leveraging innovative technologies that adhere to the hierarchy of controls. The GRDC is specifically interested in proposals that prioritise the elimination of hazards at their source, moving beyond reliance on behavioural adjustments or administrative controls. Technological solutions—particularly those driven by automation and connected systems—are anticipated to play a crucial role in reducing safety risks and advancing the industry’s overall safety standards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/b16cd77e-d5b5-4186-804a-5b828794f8eb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ6592-1: ESTJ2092PH1 (JP2092PH1) Guided Weapons Explosive Ordnance Enterprise Program - DSC Invitation to Register</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/032ed461-812c-4df1-8635-165435f2d6b5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Guided Weapons Explosive Ordnance Enterprise (Program of Works) (PoW) – Design Services Contract (DSC) – Invitation to Register Interest (ITR)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The 2024 National Defence Strategy placed renewed focus on ADFs Guided Weapons and Explosive Ordnance (GWEO) Capability with a requirement to build stocks, strengthen supply chains and manufacture munitions in Australia.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This Project will support the Government’s direction to increase the Guided Weapons and Explosive Ordnance Capability by providing the facilities and infrastructure required to manage, store, and maintain munitions throughout Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The proposed scope of works is a continuation of the existing ESTJP2093PH1 / JP2092PH1 Guided Weapons Explosive Ordnance Storage Program&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/032ed461-812c-4df1-8635-165435f2d6b5</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JHC/RFP/2025/1: Australian Defence Contracted Health System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3683550e-e656-47ab-a630-eca1e3c6f712</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Request for Proposal for the Australian Defence Contracted Health System&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3683550e-e656-47ab-a630-eca1e3c6f712</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFAT-1074: Pacific Lead Economist</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6c3aae79-a849-4799-9656-07025cd94f65</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Pacific Lead Economist is an important role providing expert advice on broad economic issues in the Pacific Region.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6c3aae79-a849-4799-9656-07025cd94f65</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E24-47488: Provision of Cyber Security Services for the Department of Health, Disability and Ageing.</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5c3d998d-6938-4aad-95b4-733354caf24b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health, Disability and Ageing is seeking to engage a qualified and experienced Cyber Security Partner to deliver specialised services within a complex multi-vendor ICT environment. Core responsibilities will include managing Security Operations Centre (SOC) functions, leading incident response activities, and administering SIEM, SOAR, and vulnerability management platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5c3d998d-6938-4aad-95b4-733354caf24b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_4736: To establish Contract for Revision of mercury in freshwater and marine water default guidelines values (DGVs)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/97858b1f-a173-4c08-ad64-563d7100369a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Revision of mercury (total mercury, organic, and inorganic) in freshwater and marine water default guidelines values (DGVs)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/97858b1f-a173-4c08-ad64-563d7100369a</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177308: Biosecurity preparedness for Wheat Blast - Identifying new genetic solutions and bolstering Australian expertise</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/77e61cb7-80f4-408b-8c3f-3cca363ef5e1</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This investment aims to enhance Australian preparedness for wheat blast by identifying new durable genetic solutions through collaboration with international specialists. A postdoctoral scientist will work with global experts to discover new sources of resistance and develop genetic selection tools, which will be disseminated to Australian researchers and breeders. Although primarily affiliated with an Australian organisation, the postdoctoral researcher will undertake a portion of their work overseas in partnership with international collaborators. Additionally, the investment will support a proportion of full-time equivalent (FTE) of the principal supervisor, who will be based within the Australian organisation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/77e61cb7-80f4-408b-8c3f-3cca363ef5e1</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2024_3275: NatHERS for existing homes - Assessor Accreditation Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9ce8f3ba-d531-419b-929d-6275e213b11c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Seeking to engage one or more organisations to provide assessor accreditation services for the expansion of the Nationwide House Energy Rating Scheme (NatHERS) to existing homes. The organisation will need to accredit and manage the ongoing accreditation of energy assessors, on behalf of the NatHERS Administrator and in accordance with standards and procedures established by the NatHERS Administrator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9ce8f3ba-d531-419b-929d-6275e213b11c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177329: Quantifying potential benefits of strategic and tactical fallowing in Western Australia</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/fce9ce5a-6b6b-4e73-a612-52438c8fdba6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;Long (winter) fallowing can be either strategic or tactical. In strategic fallowing the decision to fallow is made in advance and implemented regularly to manage climate risk. In tactical fallowing the decision to fallow is more reactive, based on the evolving season and can be related to seasonal risk mitigation or temporal changes in weed and disease burdens. Although many growers are implementing a (winter) fallow in their farming systems, a large number remain uncertain and are seeking scientifically backed advice on several aspects of fallowing. Recent National Grower Network (NGN) investments from GRDC have provided some insights into the costs and benefits of fallowing. But there are complexities affecting the decision to fallow and knowledge gaps on fallowing were still a priority issue raised at several NGN forums in the LRZ of Western Australia. This investment aims to provide growers with technical guidelines that provide actionable insights for considering strategic and/or tactical fallowing approaches.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/fce9ce5a-6b6b-4e73-a612-52438c8fdba6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177330: Innovative management solutions to enhance crop productivity in heavy soils in the Southern Region</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/aaff0d81-ce19-4d65-8a44-5aba90b20366</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;GRDC is seeking a lead organisation to deliver a coordinated Research, Development &amp;amp; Extension (RD&amp;amp;E) program to address constraints to profitability of heavy soils using a zonal approach for the different climatic conditions. 1) In the High Rainfall Zone, it seeks to refine and expand the adoption of proven subsoil treatments through large-scale, monitored demonstration trials and barrier-specific extension activities. 2) In the Medium and Low Rainfall Zones, the focus is on pioneering topsoil amelioration methods, such as surface-applied amendments and shallow reengineering techniques, to address surface sealing and hard-setting more cost-effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/aaff0d81-ce19-4d65-8a44-5aba90b20366</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proc-9177285: Research Seed Multiplication Program - Secondary Site</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/27baa6fd-04d7-4d7e-8876-f380476f366b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Research Seed Multiplication Program has been developed to enable the success and return on investment for many high-value GRDC research investments. These investments rely on the sourcing of high-quality seed to achieve project outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Research Seed Multiplication Program will ensure consistent delivery of seed of commercial varieties of wheat, barley, durum, oat, chickpea, lentil, lupin, faba bean and field pea to various research projects across Australia in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aim of the project is to provide multiple secondary sources of seed for GRDC research investments, including NVT, to build redundancy into the program and assist in mitigating the risks associated with a single site and Service Provider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project will require reliable production sites, situated in appropriate geographic regions, to minimise risk of crop failure. Sites will contain all open-pollinated commercial varieties required nationally for the NVT project that year and will be used to provide seed to NVT Service Providers and GRDC researchers, along with surplus seed being retained into cold storage as a backup seed source in case of subsequent season failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This procurement will source, through an open market approach, a Service Provider who has the appropriate technical skills and experience to deliver the project outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/27baa6fd-04d7-4d7e-8876-f380476f366b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ6584: LAND8710PH5 Littoral Manoeuvre Program – Facilities</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e52a4443-699c-4796-bbf1-b9d4a3dd6de4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LAND8710PH5 Littoral Manoeuvre Program – Facilities - Future Procurement Notice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e52a4443-699c-4796-bbf1-b9d4a3dd6de4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DemoATM2025: Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGF_17: Supply of Medical Grade Footwear to eligible persons</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NOTE: existing suppliers need not reapply&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Medical Grade Footwear (MGF) Programme is an important part of DVA’s health care arrangements and is part of the Rehabilitation Appliance Programme (RAP).&amp;nbsp; The MGF Programme provides a nation-wide access to a wide range of MGF and related services for entitled persons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPC-2017: Invitation to provide Day Procedure Centre Services to the Veteran Community</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Veterans’ Affairs (DVA) is seeking to contract with eligible stand-alone private day hospitals (referred to as Day Procedure Centres or DPCs) to provide DPC services for DVA Entitled Persons across Australia from 1 October 2017 onwards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHS-16: Private Hospital Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DVA is seeking the provision of Private Hospital services for Entitled Persons by publishing this &lt;em&gt;Invitation to Provide Private Hospital Services to the Veteran Community&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNS16: Department of Veterans' Affairs Community Nursing Services Invitation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Department of Veterans' Affairs invites interested suppliers of Community Nursing Services to apply to provide these services from 1 July 2016.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>