<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <atom:link href="https://www.tenders.gov.au#rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <title>AusTender Current ATM List</title>
    <language>en-AU</language>
    <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/List</link>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 16:35:14 GMT</lastBuildDate>
    <description>AusTender Current ATM List</description>
    <item>
      <title>PIN_2025_0243: Solar Battery Testing</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e575a2dc-a2f5-481e-ba0a-333e3214f74b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Solar battery testing program under the Small-scale Renewable Energy Scheme&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e575a2dc-a2f5-481e-ba0a-333e3214f74b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT-2026-0031: Wellbeing Services for FCFCOA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/689a49fd-f480-4ba6-9125-6f7664341fb6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Wellbeing Services for FCFCOA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/689a49fd-f480-4ba6-9125-6f7664341fb6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025/2656: Boodjamulla-Croydon seismic data processing</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7d72fe4f-f16e-4851-9811-7937ec27f84f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Process ~842 km of high-fold, long-offset 2D seismic data using two different parameter sets. The first dataset has a record length of 6 s and will be processed to focus on near-surface and shallow structures up to 2–3 s. The second dataset has a record length of 20 s and will be processed through two separate workflows, producing outputs at 8 s and 20 s&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7d72fe4f-f16e-4851-9811-7937ec27f84f</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>INFRA SLRCI 2025: Pre-tender industry briefing notice for stormwater, landslide and rockfall mitigation works on Christmas Island</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8181b25e-39fb-48d5-81f2-5baa85fda86b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Infrastructure, Transport, Regional Development, Communications, Sport and the Arts invites attendance at a pre-tender industry briefing to advise on the anticipated RFT for the provision of design, planning and construction services for stormwater, landslide and rockfall mitigation project under an Early Contractor Involvement model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8181b25e-39fb-48d5-81f2-5baa85fda86b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2187/RFT: National Maintenance Services: Enforcement Communication System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d86eb729-a5a2-4330-ab64-80f5bb25f57a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Home Affairs seeks to engage a suitably skilled and qualified Supplier to provide ongoing support and maintenance services for its Enforcement Communications System, including all equipment and services necessary to provide the services.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d86eb729-a5a2-4330-ab64-80f5bb25f57a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177330: Innovative management solutions to enhance crop productivity in heavy soils in the Southern Region</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/aaff0d81-ce19-4d65-8a44-5aba90b20366</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;GRDC is seeking a lead organisation to deliver a coordinated Research, Development &amp;amp; Extension (RD&amp;amp;E) program to address constraints to profitability of heavy soils using a zonal approach for the different climatic conditions. 1) In the High Rainfall Zone, it seeks to refine and expand the adoption of proven subsoil treatments through large-scale, monitored demonstration trials and barrier-specific extension activities. 2) In the Medium and Low Rainfall Zones, the focus is on pioneering topsoil amelioration methods, such as surface-applied amendments and shallow reengineering techniques, to address surface sealing and hard-setting more cost-effectively.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/aaff0d81-ce19-4d65-8a44-5aba90b20366</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROCFY25156: Tourism Australia - Global Media Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b8647d5-f56f-47e3-8ab2-f2b0366bbff7</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tourism Australia - Global Media Services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b8647d5-f56f-47e3-8ab2-f2b0366bbff7</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10541: Campbell Barracks Multiple Minor Works, WA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b3baac60-ce2b-43ea-b14f-ec8fab66eaf4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Campbell Barracks Multiple Minor Works, WA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b3baac60-ce2b-43ea-b14f-ec8fab66eaf4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HOMEAFFAIRS/2194/RFI: Stage 1 - Request for Information (RFI) Freedom of Information and Privacy (FOIP) Case Management Capability</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c5c63e21-0e05-47ba-9425-b5d1d5c164d6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Stage 1 - RFI is released by the Department with the aim of engaging with industry to inform the Department’s requirements for the provision of a solution that will support the management of the FOIP business requests, and to examine best Respondents for the Stage 2 – Request for Tender (RFT).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c5c63e21-0e05-47ba-9425-b5d1d5c164d6</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Proc-9177285: Research Seed Multiplication Program - Secondary Site</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/27baa6fd-04d7-4d7e-8876-f380476f366b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Research Seed Multiplication Program has been developed to enable the success and return on investment for many high-value GRDC research investments. These investments rely on the sourcing of high-quality seed to achieve project outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Research Seed Multiplication Program will ensure consistent delivery of seed of commercial varieties of wheat, barley, durum, oat, chickpea, lentil, lupin, faba bean and field pea to various research projects across Australia in a timely manner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The aim of the project is to provide multiple secondary sources of seed for GRDC research investments, including NVT, to build redundancy into the program and assist in mitigating the risks associated with a single site and Service Provider.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The project will require reliable production sites, situated in appropriate geographic regions, to minimise risk of crop failure. Sites will contain all open-pollinated commercial varieties required nationally for the NVT project that year and will be used to provide seed to NVT Service Providers and GRDC researchers, along with surplus seed being retained into cold storage as a backup seed source in case of subsequent season failure.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This procurement will source, through an open market approach, a Service Provider who has the appropriate technical skills and experience to deliver the project outcomes.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/27baa6fd-04d7-4d7e-8876-f380476f366b</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ6601: Head Contract for Work Package 2.4 Henderson WA Remediate Storage Capacity</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2229b9bb-4bf1-4edb-b19e-8aa43e48b401</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Invitation to Register Interest for Head Contract (HC-1) ESTJ8218 - Expand Storage Capacity - Work Package 2.4, Theatre Logistics WA.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2229b9bb-4bf1-4edb-b19e-8aa43e48b401</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10689: Mount Stuart Training Area Road Works, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/32740d4b-0383-4077-b456-71eb945afddd</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;EST10689 Mount Stuart Training Area Road Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/32740d4b-0383-4077-b456-71eb945afddd</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIRORFT2025010: Tidbinbilla Oil Tanks – Design, Construct and Remediation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ac83c105-b06a-4d04-8cde-4cf935bbe024</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;CSIRO is seeking responses from suitably qualified and experienced providers for the design and construct of an above ground oil tank system to include pipework, pumps, filter and electrical services to serve DSS-43 antenna.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ac83c105-b06a-4d04-8cde-4cf935bbe024</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>5393-2025-26: CliDE WIS2Box Station Chaining</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cd45a995-f48c-47f8-9fd4-21a54ae03785</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision for CliDE WIS2Box Station Chaining services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cd45a995-f48c-47f8-9fd4-21a54ae03785</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DACPROC25/015: Approach the Market (ATM) for the provision of e-serial publication subscriptions for the library.</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e8f24269-c070-4124-a737-5791f5117ca3</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This Approach to Market (ATM) is for the provision of access to e-Serial publications and related services to support the Department of Foreign Affairs and Trade’s ongoing information needs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e8f24269-c070-4124-a737-5791f5117ca3</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OOSGG 2025 Insignia: Manufacture and supply of Insignia, Warrant Folders and Presentation Cases for Australian Honours and Awards</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/81a01674-5027-4161-a28d-76fed95f5801</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This approach to market is for the manufacture and supply of insignia, warrant folders and presentation cases for Australian Honours and Awards and the Governor-General's Challenge Coins.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/81a01674-5027-4161-a28d-76fed95f5801</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTA-RFT-61596: Whole of Australian Government Microsoft Licensing Solution Provider Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/62cf9b88-3984-486f-a744-ec2d58398741</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Request for Tender for a Whole of Government Licence Solution Provider to support the Microsoft Volume Sourcing Arrangement&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/62cf9b88-3984-486f-a744-ec2d58398741</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10692: Cowley Beach Training Area Road Maintenance, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/09f693cf-ed04-4bfb-82dd-27debe96f16b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cowley Beach Training Area Road Maintenance, QLD&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/09f693cf-ed04-4bfb-82dd-27debe96f16b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09268: Gallipoli Barracks Building Refurbishments, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2cd20b76-9333-4374-974a-65581447c72c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gallipoli Barracks Building Refurbishment Works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/2cd20b76-9333-4374-974a-65581447c72c</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST07484: RAAF Edinburgh Building Refurbishment, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a0b65000-3b64-444c-a3ba-0695a6e4e25b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;RAAF Edinburgh Building Refurbishment, SA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a0b65000-3b64-444c-a3ba-0695a6e4e25b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CD/NOT/27857/1: Defence Capability Support Panel (DCSP) -  Pre-Release Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/76caedef-b0eb-43ed-b0cb-c05f3b2224e5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Pre-Release Notice for the Defence Capability Support Panel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/76caedef-b0eb-43ed-b0cb-c05f3b2224e5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSC002537: Cleaning Services - Clayton</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3c0ccff9-c7df-4049-bfed-750129f4cc0d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cleaning Services - Clayton (VIC)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3c0ccff9-c7df-4049-bfed-750129f4cc0d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09335: Port Wakefield General Building &amp; Road Works, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/52fcc784-025e-4da2-8ed9-a89dc9e02dc0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Port Wakefield General Building &amp;amp; Road Works, SA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/52fcc784-025e-4da2-8ed9-a89dc9e02dc0</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2024_3275: NatHERS for existing homes - Assessor Accreditation Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9ce8f3ba-d531-419b-929d-6275e213b11c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Seeking to engage one or more organisations to provide assessor accreditation services for the expansion of the Nationwide House Energy Rating Scheme (NatHERS) to existing homes. The organisation will need to accredit and manage the ongoing accreditation of energy assessors, on behalf of the NatHERS Administrator and in accordance with standards and procedures established by the NatHERS Administrator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9ce8f3ba-d531-419b-929d-6275e213b11c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM 2025 2455: Procurement of a Trace Moisture Analyser</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/024a1cd9-bb56-4a82-8116-9fad7f26bd52</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Reference Gas Mixtures section of the National Measurement Institute’s Chemical and Biological Branch requires a trace moisture analyser to measure water content in gases.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/024a1cd9-bb56-4a82-8116-9fad7f26bd52</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10526: DSTG Edinburgh Demolition &amp; Refurbishment Works, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bfa2ccc8-fa78-4216-8a0a-db0be458b052</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DSTG Edinburgh Demolition &amp;amp; Refurbishment Works, SA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/bfa2ccc8-fa78-4216-8a0a-db0be458b052</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASQA_2025-26_6283: ASQA Regulatory Panel (Service Pillar 1) – Student Assessment Validations</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6bf24236-1802-484e-8719-7454b95363fa</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ASQA Regulatory Panel (Service Pillar 1) – Student Assessment Validations&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6bf24236-1802-484e-8719-7454b95363fa</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E25-227849: RFT for the provision of the development of national clinical guidelines for menopause and perimenopause</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7837be44-50ef-4ba5-827f-d97d732278b0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health, Disability and Ageing is seeking to engage a supplier to&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;to develop new national clinical practice guidelines for perimenopause and menopause.&amp;nbsp; It is expected that the guidelines may be ‘living guidelines’. The guidelines must be developed in accordance with the 2016 National Health and Medical Research Council’s (NHMRC) Standards for Guidelines and be approved by NHMRC.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7837be44-50ef-4ba5-827f-d97d732278b0</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AUS2025 IntMedia RFT: International Media Buying Services Panel 2025 OT</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9b3d848d-deb1-408f-a50f-abcdab41c6b2</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Lead Customer is proposing to establish a Standing Offer Arrangement to cover International Media Buying services with one or more suitable suppliers that can meet the needs outlined below for the term of the proposed Standing Offer Arrangement plus any extension options.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The lead customer will undertake an international Media Buy Panel Request for quote (RFQ) process with the supplier for set pieces of work as required. Responses to these requests by the supplier must provide and maintain the service levels, pricing and overall value for money consistent with the terms/conditions/offerings in the overarching Standing Offer Arrangement.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9b3d848d-deb1-408f-a50f-abcdab41c6b2</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025/1315: Well Data and Analysis Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d7de2320-aa93-4ed6-b525-0fd7f7d74e5b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Standing Offer Arrangement to cover Geoscience Australia's requirements include the examination and analysis of legacy well information, both physical and digital, to make data more accessible and useable for exploration and research users. All of Australia’s onshore and offshore petroleum and stratigraphic wells will be considered, and approximately 400 wells will be analysed over the next 10 years. The life of the project is currently planned to be at least 10 years with two data releases per year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d7de2320-aa93-4ed6-b525-0fd7f7d74e5b</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177339: Understanding GRDC's opportunities to leverage existing data repositories and facilitate data aggregation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/28cff864-6438-4899-9c6a-5970419b20d4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GRDC’s strategy for RD&amp;amp;E data management focuses on improving the visibility and accessibility of its data assets by leveraging distributed data storage repositories that meet GRDC criteria (approved repositories GRDC also recognises that there are other repositories that specialise in specific scientific domains, such as AusPestCheck and the Atlas of Living Australia for pest monitoring data or NCBI for genetics research. These repositories enhance data interoperability and aggregation opportunities through standardised metadata and formatting. However, GRDC lacks a comprehensive understanding of the extent to which these repositories are used by research partners, whether they align with GRDC’s Criteria for Approved Repositories and how they may facilitate interoperability. This consultancy will assess existing data platforms and repositories, ensuring that GRDC adopts an effective and sustainable data aggregation strategy that supports interoperability across research domains.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/28cff864-6438-4899-9c6a-5970419b20d4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_RFI 2025/3141: Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning technologies for archival workflows</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6da68ba4-f347-4899-8ddf-3e478b2ac536</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;National Archives seeks to conduct and evaluate technology pilots utilising Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning technologies across the following areas:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Transcription&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Description&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Access Examination&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;•&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Search &amp;amp; Discovery&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this approach to market is to explore and identify a shortlist of solutions that meet the high-level business objectives of National Archives but are purposefully not prescriptive in the design or technical specification of what might underpin those solutions. Shortlisted vendors will be invited to participate in a future approach to market to select and procure specific solution/s.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6da68ba4-f347-4899-8ddf-3e478b2ac536</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177342: Australian Grains Innovation Program 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/86ffda52-4c5b-4e94-8718-330ff3939904</link>
      <description>&lt;p class="MsoNormal"&gt;The &amp;lsquo;Australian Grains Innovation Program&amp;rsquo; consists of two pillars, the pre-accelerator commercialisation, and accelerator foundational phases of technology commercialisation and startup development. These pillars complement each other in the progression of innovation development and commercialisation, building a supportive framework for ideas to be identified and tested early in a pre-accelerator environment before further resource may be put towards technology and business development, and growth in an accelerator.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/86ffda52-4c5b-4e94-8718-330ff3939904</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PSC002545: Provision of Labour Hire Services to ANSTO</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4da9d512-18d6-4c75-b9a6-227ace442b69</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;ANSTO is seeking responses from suitably qualified and experienced vendors for the provision of Labour Hire Services to ANSTO&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4da9d512-18d6-4c75-b9a6-227ace442b69</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08351: HMAS Albatross Accommodation Building Works, NSW</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a871aa17-6290-4fb4-8b58-342e7246d84b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Albatross Accommodation Building Works, NSW&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/a871aa17-6290-4fb4-8b58-342e7246d84b</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4771-2024-25: Brisbane Airport Secondary AWS Siteworks</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8951ea27-5f76-4258-b100-0c6e77f1a830</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision for Brisbane Airport Secondary AWS Siteworks&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8951ea27-5f76-4258-b100-0c6e77f1a830</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NNSD/RFT/69114/1: HDP Site Characterisation Reports Procurement</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c4c1853d-b39a-4b26-9b53-fb1efac04fa8</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence is seeking an Infrastructure Engineering Organisation to develop twenty-five site investigation and reports.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c4c1853d-b39a-4b26-9b53-fb1efac04fa8</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land4140S3CCISTS-2V1: Land4140 Submission 3 Capability Challenge</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6dd573d0-fdef-4a91-a2f8-53cfb659a8cd</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The LC4 Program is seeking industry proposals for innovative, interoperable, and scalable solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6dd573d0-fdef-4a91-a2f8-53cfb659a8cd</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM 2025 2336: Procurement for Cross Divisional Financial and Market Data Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b95dc6aa-e87b-4024-9bb4-55c1f4ea869f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DISR requires access to comprehensive, reliable, and real-time financial and market data services to support its policy, research and analytical functions. We seek a data service that provides access to high-quality, real time and historical datasets, analysis and analytical tools to enable evidence-based decision making through an informed understanding of: • domestic and international markets across a range of business entities • economic conditions in Australian industries, including to assess whether the Australian market is, or may experience, injury because of anti-competitive behaviour • the international competitiveness of Australia’s resources and heavy industry sectors in the context of a decarbonising world economy • emerging industry risks. The data service must be delivered through either a desktop browser, a secure online platform, terminal access across multiple locations and/or an API with sufficient functionality to meet the needs of geographically dispersed officers within DISR.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b95dc6aa-e87b-4024-9bb4-55c1f4ea869f</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFAT-1072: Australia Awards Myanmar</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7a481f8d-2582-4ddc-b400-4fe8aa1b8b47</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Australia Awards Myanmar&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7a481f8d-2582-4ddc-b400-4fe8aa1b8b47</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Notice 2025/002: Notice for Main Works Contractor Services for the AIS Podium Project</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/10eef0e6-7373-41c8-b09e-b0c3ec57d06e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Australian Sports Commission (ASC) is issuing this Notice of Intended Procurement (NOIP) for the upcoming Australian Institute of Sport (AIS) Podium Project.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/10eef0e6-7373-41c8-b09e-b0c3ec57d06e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/ PH25/14904: National Immunisation Program – Technical, Research and Essential Program Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3519ce93-cc23-47a9-8d2f-2607be317c5c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The Department of Health, Disability and Ageing (the Department) is seeking to advise the market of its upcoming intention to procure one or more service providers to deliver &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Technical, Research and Essential Program Services for the National Immunisation Program (NIP). &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;These services are intended to support the Department with administering the NIP covering key subject areas including program support, vaccine safety, communications and engagement and program data, analysis and research. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The request for tender is expected to be released late October 2025&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3519ce93-cc23-47a9-8d2f-2607be317c5c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GA2025/1556: Inorganic Geochemistry and X-ray Diffraction Analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dbaef0c5-d124-4f43-9949-34f1d2b618c6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Geoscience Australia (GA), as part of the Birrindudu Deep Dive (BDD) project, requires multi-elemental geochemical data on 460 to 700 whole-rock samples per service, provided as&amp;nbsp;prepared rock powders. The required services include:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Service A&amp;nbsp;– Whole Rock Inorganic Geochemistry Analysis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;·&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; Service B&amp;nbsp;– Whole Rock Quantitative XRD Analysis&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Suppliers can provide a response for only Service A or only Service B or both services (Services A and B).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dbaef0c5-d124-4f43-9949-34f1d2b618c6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST09254-1: Woomera Building Refurbishment, SA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ec1ed6cf-a704-4134-95a5-4c8142039563</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Woomera Building Refurbishment&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ec1ed6cf-a704-4134-95a5-4c8142039563</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRH 25/26 DHOAS: Defence Home Ownership Assistance Scheme (DHOAS)</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cf5507c0-0060-481e-993f-c19c4beb8ab6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence Home Ownership Assistance Scheme (DHOAS) to ADF Members and Veterans&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/cf5507c0-0060-481e-993f-c19c4beb8ab6</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/ PH25-14909: Immunisation services for the Australian Centre for Disease Control and the Department of Health, Disability and Ageing</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dec9d0c9-de4b-49e7-ba87-b5f0269c70ea</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health, Disability and Ageing (the department) is seeking to advise the market of its intention to procure technical immunisation services for the department and the future Australian Centre for Disease Control (Australian CDC).&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This procurement aims to secure technical expertise to support the future Australian CDC and the department including in enhancing preparedness for public health emergencies, strengthening national public health surveillance, health security, and supporting technical committees to develop immunisation policies and guidance for Australia.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The request for tender is expected to be released in late October 2025.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dec9d0c9-de4b-49e7-ba87-b5f0269c70ea</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_2391: Gravimetric Laboratory Sample Preparation Robot</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0b2634af-038a-493a-9e32-77aa7705582f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The department is seeking to acquire a gravimetric laboratory sample preparation robot for microwave digestion workflows in support of ICP-MS analysis.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/0b2634af-038a-493a-9e32-77aa7705582f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM 2025 2450: Procurement of Glove Box</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6b8d0cd7-05ab-4c01-957d-9d1b241c5116</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Measurement Institute (NMI) requires the procurement of a contract for a glove box for the Reference Gas Mixtures laboratory at NMI Lindfield to complement the existing fume hoods within their state-of-the-art gas facility.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6b8d0cd7-05ab-4c01-957d-9d1b241c5116</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E25-268523: Participant travel support service for the National Lung Cancer Screening Program</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8ce87c3d-2489-46bf-af5c-8160abb4c608</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health, Disability and Ageing is seeking to procure an organisation to design, promote, coordinate and deliver a national travel support service for rural and remote participants of the National Lung Cancer Screening Program.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8ce87c3d-2489-46bf-af5c-8160abb4c608</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctic ATM25/2482: ATM 25/2482 - Snow Blowers for Trial in Antarctica</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aa5912f4-8c63-4d85-bd2b-fa66a02afbf7</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of a snow blower/snow blowers to the Australian Antarctic Division.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aa5912f4-8c63-4d85-bd2b-fa66a02afbf7</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PRN2024-966: Online Mindfulness Program</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aa654fca-3439-4fce-bdb4-d54bdc7387e6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Veterans' Affairs requests suitable organisations to tender for the delivery of an Online Mindfulness program for veterans and veteran family members.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/aa654fca-3439-4fce-bdb4-d54bdc7387e6</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTA-ICT-71267: Data Centre Panel Refresh</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/03c3f090-23f5-4868-9d27-cde25b493be3</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Supply of data centre facilities (including collocated facilities) and prefabricated data centres.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/03c3f090-23f5-4868-9d27-cde25b493be3</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60432: Air Transport Standing Offer for Services - Request for Tender</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ea361613-b84e-4e78-b1fa-f23c48ec7e4b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Air Transport Standing Offer for Services - Request for Tender&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ea361613-b84e-4e78-b1fa-f23c48ec7e4b</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AZ6584: LAND8710PH5 Littoral Manoeuvre Program – Facilities</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e52a4443-699c-4796-bbf1-b9d4a3dd6de4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;LAND8710PH5 Littoral Manoeuvre Program – Facilities - Future Procurement Notice.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e52a4443-699c-4796-bbf1-b9d4a3dd6de4</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Apr 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFQ 2025-26 002: Impact Investing Demonstration Fund</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/e6ee2604-8ed7-4192-8b61-4a3240f460ce</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Creative Australia is the Australian Government’s principal arts investment and advisory body. We are currently seeking quotes for preparatory work required to deliver the &lt;strong&gt;Impact Investing Demonstration Fund&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Impact Investing Demonstration Fund represents a strategic initiative by Creative Australia to catalyse new pathways for financing the arts and creative industries by mobilising repayable capital in pursuit of cultural, social, and economic outcomes.&amp;nbsp;In alignment with the National Cultural Policy &lt;em&gt;Revive&lt;/em&gt;, and Creative Australia’s legislative mandate, this initiative introduces impact investing as a complementary mechanism to traditional grant-making.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/e6ee2604-8ed7-4192-8b61-4a3240f460ce</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NAVY/TF/PCS/58351: Performance Coaching Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/22812c2b-6296-4137-ae0f-822430ac9f93</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Performance Coaching Services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/22812c2b-6296-4137-ae0f-822430ac9f93</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_5410: Addressing information gaps on little penguins to support offshore wind</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/62f44882-05e7-4e9d-9f35-628fd10eae67</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This project seeks to generate targeted information to support decision-making by assessment officers and project proponents under the Environment Protection and Biodiversity Conservation Act 1999 (EPBC Act).&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The research will investigate risks and potential impact pathways to little penguins (Eudyptula minor) arising from offshore wind farms and associated port developments in Australia. The findings will inform effective mitigation and management strategies, enabling regulators and industry to assess renewable energy projects under the EPBC Act with greater speed and scientific rigour. For further details, refer to the associated ATM documentation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/62f44882-05e7-4e9d-9f35-628fd10eae67</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHFT24022: CI Barging Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6d0bc8b0-b661-45d2-be90-034405163789</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Barging Services (Cockatoo Island)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6d0bc8b0-b661-45d2-be90-034405163789</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SPC-15936: Supply of Legal Document Management Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7a31be2b-1d91-4cce-a513-6599a8628c60</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The ATO has a need for Legal Document Management Services, specifically for processing, coding and converting files into a format compatible for upload onto Nuix Discover.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7a31be2b-1d91-4cce-a513-6599a8628c60</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11249: To establish a Contract for Booderee National Park: Cultural Centre Business Case</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b979663-d377-45fb-9a74-ca852c493844</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of: professional services to develop a business case assessing the viability of a Cultural Centre within Booderee National Park.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7b979663-d377-45fb-9a74-ca852c493844</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177343: A Soils Educational Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/7cff692f-8d1a-49d5-ac12-ec95588053c0</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The opportunity for Australian grains growers to leverage both old and newly emerging soils and nutrition research is vast and promising. Understanding the physical, chemical and biological properties of soils and their interactions is key to managing soils to their full production potential.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/7cff692f-8d1a-49d5-ac12-ec95588053c0</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E25-431570: Molecular Testing to support the Australian Clinical Guidelines on HTLV-1 for Aboriginal Primary Health Care Settings</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fcb20911-2c3c-4bbf-956b-9e054fab4a60</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health, Disability and Ageing is seeking to procure services for:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;1. Proviral load (PVL) testing services as per the current HTLV-1 Guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2. If necessary, a project to fill any gap or gaps for HTLV-1 testing and HTLV-1 PVL testing arising from the current HTLV-1 Guidelines.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fcb20911-2c3c-4bbf-956b-9e054fab4a60</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTA-ICT-74060: Cloud Marketplace Refresh</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/24714bb0-ae71-47c6-9a0b-2682b79b67a9</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We are undertaking a refresh of the Cloud Marketplace to allow for potential suppliers that wish to provide Offerings that meet the requirements specified in this Application Process to apply to become a Seller under the Cloud Marketplace. This Application Process allows Applicants (You) to apply to supply Offerings within the scope of Cloud Services and Cloud Consulting. Cloud Services Category includes ICT functionality (‘as a service’) services available aligned with the classification, characteristics and deployment models of ISO/IEC 17788. Cloud Consulting includes cloud computing related professional services through subject matter experts to assist on Cloud initiatives with the skills and capabilities aligned to levels 3-7 of the Skills for the Information Age (SFIA) framework.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/24714bb0-ae71-47c6-9a0b-2682b79b67a9</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DTA-RFT-61588: Digital Marketplace Panel 2, Software and Cloud – Notice of public consultation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e402aaea-5813-4416-a8e8-4d53df8b5436</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;An invitation to engage in public consultation on the draft terms for Software and Cloud under the Digital Marketplace Panel 2 has been released on BuyICT.gov.au&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/e402aaea-5813-4416-a8e8-4d53df8b5436</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFMA25-26-1: Request for Tender to establish a Panel Arrangement for the supply of Electronic Monitoring equipment on fishing vessels</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3a3d1c11-a481-4764-9444-afe9943937c9</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Establish a Panel Arrangement with EM Providers for fisheries electronic monitoring equipment and associated services under a standards-based model.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3a3d1c11-a481-4764-9444-afe9943937c9</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESE25/8988: Request for Tender in relation to data services for the Programme for the International Assessment of Adult Competencies</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d9b69f14-627f-4f40-8d99-d617af780f4f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Programme for the International Assessment of Adult Competencies (PIAAC)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d9b69f14-627f-4f40-8d99-d617af780f4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST10712: Royal Military College Duntroon Building Refurbishment Works, ACT</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5644c1b1-b601-4932-b59b-390aab6f418a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Royal Military College Duntroon Building Refurbishment Works, ACT&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5644c1b1-b601-4932-b59b-390aab6f418a</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08234: HMAS Stirling Building Works, WA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dcb3ea5a-8a53-41c5-b408-8c85ec9aec4f</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Stirling Building Works, WA&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/dcb3ea5a-8a53-41c5-b408-8c85ec9aec4f</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health/E25-265571: Provision of IT Service Desk services for the Department of Health, Disability and Ageing</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/37dda9e4-3689-4e60-bee1-ce8358cee0ee</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Health, Disability and Ageing is seeking to engage a qualified and experienced Service Provider (ITSD Partner) to deliver Managed IT Service Desk (ITSD) within a complex multi vendor environment (MVE).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The ITSD Partner will be responsible for providing Level 1 support services, acting as the first point of contact for IT related incidents and service requests. The services will be delivered in alignment with the Department’s Service Integration and Management (SIAM) model and will support a multi-channel communication approach including phone, email, web-chat and self service portals.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/37dda9e4-3689-4e60-bee1-ce8358cee0ee</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM 2025 2172: To establish Contract for Procurement of the Thermogravimetric Analyser</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1992f264-2a11-4760-b3ee-3b074ccd8beb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Chemical Reference Materials section of the National Measurement Institute’s Chemical and Biological Branch requires a thermogravimetric analyser to identify thermal stability, composition, and decomposition patterns.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/1992f264-2a11-4760-b3ee-3b074ccd8beb</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NOTICE DHA-86210: NOTICE OF INTENDED PROCUREMENT - SUPPLIER EOI FOR DWELLING RELOCATION IN TOWNSVILLE, QLD</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/20b0de38-02f1-4adb-9ccd-fae2d6e6779a</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Defence Housing Australia (DHA) is issuing this Notice of Intended Procurement (NOIP) for our upcoming Townsville - QLD Aitkenvale Dwelling Relocation Expression of Interest (EOI).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/20b0de38-02f1-4adb-9ccd-fae2d6e6779a</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10018700: Managed Print Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8847e973-6e0d-43be-8273-c6b3e8c0becc</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Document reproduction services - managed print services&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/8847e973-6e0d-43be-8273-c6b3e8c0becc</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 05-2026: Supply of Northern Command Headquarters facility</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d72aa4be-78bb-490b-921c-903948524e80</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this RFT is to invite potential suppliers to submit their responses for the supply of the Northern Command Headquarters facilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d72aa4be-78bb-490b-921c-903948524e80</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>H25/716/02-OT: Health Insurance brokerage Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ae647c9-10b1-4df5-8d8b-03d32b30a30b</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Reserve Bank of Australia (the Bank) invites Proposals for the provision of health insurance brokerage services for the Australian employees and their families working overseas, in accordance with the terms and conditions of this Request for Proposal (RFP).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/6ae647c9-10b1-4df5-8d8b-03d32b30a30b</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>11692: Plumbing and septic pump out services at Booderee National Park</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/291dff00-8be5-4e77-9090-4444ee767197</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Request for Tender to establish a Deed of Standing Offer for plumbing and septic pump out services at Booderee National Park.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/291dff00-8be5-4e77-9090-4444ee767197</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-5667: Request for Tender for the provision of a Talent and Learning Management System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9e87f274-3cc0-4d0c-846e-0d1594c9a017</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Talent and Learning Management System&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/9e87f274-3cc0-4d0c-846e-0d1594c9a017</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Health RF/PH25/13765: Request for Information for the National One Stop Shop ICT Solution for Health and Medical Research</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/43020567-117a-46b6-8d90-bef7acc075cf</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;National One Stop Shop for health and medical research&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/43020567-117a-46b6-8d90-bef7acc075cf</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_4897: Development of a Climate Change Explanatory Note and Summary</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/44a8e748-9d36-4653-84f1-f85d23472e7e</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Office of Water Science on behalf of the Independent Expert Scientific Committee on Unconventional Gas Development and Large Coal Mining Development (IESC) requires independent experts for the development of an Explanatory Note (EN) and Summary Guide on incorporating climate change into environmental impact assessments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/44a8e748-9d36-4653-84f1-f85d23472e7e</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>60434 Pre-Release 2: 60434 - Linguist Support to Operations Standing Offer for Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4b915b36-ab82-4ab6-9c73-3805cd19c331</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Pre-notification to industry of future RFT release&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4b915b36-ab82-4ab6-9c73-3805cd19c331</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177341: Phase 2 - Harvester set-up workshops for the economic optimisation of harvest losses, efficiency and grain quality.</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/8eba60ba-a2e9-4316-a90f-cfe6f8fcafc4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This investment is designed to deliver a national program of harvester set up workshops, assisting growers to optimise losses and machinery throughput, alongside targeted research to build capacity in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/8eba60ba-a2e9-4316-a90f-cfe6f8fcafc4</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EST08644: HMAS Stirling Training Centre Refurbishments, WA</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c8a24357-98ab-424d-b103-23bf449ed8f6</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HMAS Stirling Training Centre Refurbishment works&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c8a24357-98ab-424d-b103-23bf449ed8f6</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Antarctic ATM25/1727: Tracked trailers fitted with sideloaders</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b34ac2ae-5cbc-4655-adcd-6a9720376875</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Provision of two (2) sideloading tracked trailers to the Australian Antarctic Division&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b34ac2ae-5cbc-4655-adcd-6a9720376875</guid>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CFI-20251118: Defence Estate Capital and Sustainment Works Program Industry Briefing Notice</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b24b33ed-c388-4c41-a0a9-30946e5ee79d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Defence's Security and Estate Group invites Industry to attend the bi-annual Defence Estate and Sustainment Works Program Industry Briefing. The purpose is to provide Industry with an update on Defence estate matters, including planned upcoming procurement opportunities across capital facilities and infrastructure projects.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b24b33ed-c388-4c41-a0a9-30946e5ee79d</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RFT 01-2026: National Police Check Systems Replacement (NPCSR) Project</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c1baa20e-7193-4456-91c1-5c75acfbe553</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of this RFT is to invite potential suppliers to submit their responses for the provision of products and services to replace National Police Check (NPC) legacy systems and service desk.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/c1baa20e-7193-4456-91c1-5c75acfbe553</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NGA25-026: Customer Relationship Management and Ticketing System</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d596bca8-1861-4340-b78a-ff64c4c9eed9</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The National Gallery is seeking a Customer Relationship Management (CRM) and Ticketing System solution&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/d596bca8-1861-4340-b78a-ff64c4c9eed9</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PROC-9177354: Grain Adopt - Regional D&amp;E Open Call</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/82da7a98-0ecb-4812-9dae-b3dbae36d3cb</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GRDC is introducing this Grain Adopt – Regional D&amp;amp;E Open Call process as an additional mechanism for NGN short term responsive investments. The Open Call is an opportunity to put forward investment proposals that respond to grower-identified issues and priorities and align with GRDC’s RD&amp;amp;E Strategy.The Objective is to Identify and invest in short-term, low-risk development and extension (D&amp;amp;E) activities that address locally identified issues that are grower priorities, support adoption and problem-solving at the regional level, and deliver clear benefits to growers’ profitability, sustainability, and resilience in alignment with GRDC’s strategic priorities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Advert/Show/82da7a98-0ecb-4812-9dae-b3dbae36d3cb</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESE25/7148: Request for Tender in relation to the Programme for International Student Assessment (PISA) 2029 National Project Manage</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fe4dbed5-c974-49ef-85fe-036efd860f1d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;National Project Manager (NPM) services for Australia’s involvement in the Programme for International Student Assessment (PISA) 2029&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/fe4dbed5-c974-49ef-85fe-036efd860f1d</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFAT-1050: DEV+ Panel</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7aa7e5d1-6b12-4db0-b30f-f4dc0da8a6e4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DEV+ Panel&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7aa7e5d1-6b12-4db0-b30f-f4dc0da8a6e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ESE25/7363: WHS auditing services to deliver the Federal Safety Commissioner's WHS Accreditation Scheme</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/794c0f1c-b5bb-4f49-83d4-c103dc3c8d90</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To re establish a panel of FederalSafety Officers to deliver work health and safety auditing and ad hoc WHS advisory services to administer the Federal Safety Commissioner's Work Health and Safety Accreditation Scheme&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/794c0f1c-b5bb-4f49-83d4-c103dc3c8d90</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ATM_2025_2105: Northern Endeavour Decommissioning Phase 2 P&amp;A Well Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3dda628d-f1c2-48a0-aa6c-03c285525b6d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Northern Endeavour Phase 2 - Comprises wells permanent plug and abandonment services comprising the permanent plug and abandonment of nine wells in the Laminaria and Corallina oil field, as part of Phase 2 of the Northern Endeavour Decommissioning Program&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/3dda628d-f1c2-48a0-aa6c-03c285525b6d</guid>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A25/16: Open Space Management Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/69d41f5d-a976-4fb5-960a-dbdcef3cec9c</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Open Space Management (OSM) Services&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/69d41f5d-a976-4fb5-960a-dbdcef3cec9c</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSD/RFT/67213/1: Frigate Capability Life Cycle Manager</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b672c2f3-3bd5-45ed-94ec-e7b6070b233d</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Frigate CLCM&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/b672c2f3-3bd5-45ed-94ec-e7b6070b233d</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DemoATM2025: Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Demo ATM to test eLodgement and Download&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/7f03face-747d-481f-a7ba-0ab6dabfaa64</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MGF_17: Supply of Medical Grade Footwear to eligible persons</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;NOTE: existing suppliers need not reapply&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Medical Grade Footwear (MGF) Programme is an important part of DVA’s health care arrangements and is part of the Rehabilitation Appliance Programme (RAP).&amp;nbsp; The MGF Programme provides a nation-wide access to a wide range of MGF and related services for entitled persons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/4cbec586-e15c-3822-fba2-aab168b6d4a5</guid>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Feb 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DPC-2017: Invitation to provide Day Procedure Centre Services to the Veteran Community</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Department of Veterans’ Affairs (DVA) is seeking to contract with eligible stand-alone private day hospitals (referred to as Day Procedure Centres or DPCs) to provide DPC services for DVA Entitled Persons across Australia from 1 October 2017 onwards.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/5e64113b-fa93-08b6-3f97-0550a53cf679</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2017 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PHS-16: Private Hospital Services</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;DVA is seeking the provision of Private Hospital services for Entitled Persons by publishing this &lt;em&gt;Invitation to Provide Private Hospital Services to the Veteran Community&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/89b9dac6-0325-6a7c-78ad-4744eeb8be18</guid>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CNS16: Department of Veterans' Affairs Community Nursing Services Invitation</title>
      <link>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</link>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Department of Veterans' Affairs invites interested suppliers of Community Nursing Services to apply to provide these services from 1 July 2016.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      <guid>https://www.tenders.gov.au/Atm/Show/ed5d2e52-a2d6-b2ff-b6be-57bd37f2c8e4</guid>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>